<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>What is the most dangerous thing in your home? How can your home be made less dangerous?</item>
        <item>What is the most dangerous thing in your home for a child? How can it be made less dangerous?</item>
        <item>What dangers can be found in the kitchen that can cause accidents?</item>
        <item>What can be done to prevent kitchen accidents?</item>
        <item>What can a parent do to childproof a kitchen?</item>
        <item>What dangers can be found in bathrooms that can cause accidents?</item>
        <item>What can be done to prevent bathroom accidents?</item>
        <item>What can a parent do to childproof a bathroom?</item>
        <item>What dangers can be found outside the home in the yard that can cause accidents?</item>
        <item>What can be done to prevent yard accidents?
</item>
        <item>What can a parent do to childproof the yard?
</item>
        <item>What other dangers can be found in a home in bedrooms, laundry rooms, garages, and living areas?
</item>
        <item>What can be done throughout the house to prevent accidents?
</item>
        <item>What can a parent do to childproof the different rooms of the home?
</item>
        <item>Where at home would you put your first aid kit?
</item>
        <item>What is adoption?
</item>
        <item>Do you know anyone who was adopted as a child?
</item>
        <item>Do you know anyone who has adopted a child?
</item>
        <item>What are some of the reasons people choose to adopt?
</item>
        <item>What is the difference between domestic and international adoption?
</item>
        <item>What are the views of adoption in your country?
</item>
        <item>How would someone interested in adopting a child go about doing so?
</item>
        <item>Where do children available for adoption come from?
</item>
        <item>What happens to children that are not adopted?
</item>
        <item>Would you want to adopt a boy or a girl? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you think brothers and sisters should be separated in adoptions?
</item>
        <item>Are adoptions common in your country?
</item>
        <item>What are some organizations that help with adoptions?
</item>
        <item>Should you tell the child that he or she was adopted? If so at what age? Or when?
</item>
        <item>Should adopted children have the right to know their biological parents?
</item>
        <item>Should families with birth children also adopt?
</item>
        <item>Is the real parent the birth parent or the adoptive parent?
 </item>
        <item>Should adoptions be between children and families of the same race and or culture?
</item>
        <item>How or should the adoptive parents maintain the adopted child\'s cultural identify?
</item>
        <item>In your country are the legal rights of an adoptive child different from that of a birth child?
</item>
        <item>What are the legal consequences of adopting a child from a different race or country?
</item>
        <item>Why don\'t more people adopt children?
</item>
        <item>What makes a family, genetics or environment?
</item>
        <item>Do you support an open adoption policy where the birth parents can choose to be involved in the child\'s life?
</item>
        <item>Do you believe there is discrimination within the adoption organizations?
</item>
        <item>Do you think a person should be able to adopt a child of a different race?
</item>
        <item>Should a gay or lesbian couple be allowed to adopt a child?
</item>
        <item>Should there be an age restriction for the adoptive parents?
</item>
        <item>Should a single man or woman be able to adopt a child?
</item>
        <item>When is the right time for a child to be told that he/she was adopted?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is preferable to adopt or to use artificial reproduction technology?
</item>
        <item>Would you agree to an open adoption or closed adoption? Why?
</item>
        <item>What is an open adoption?
</item>
        <item>Would you want to find your birth family? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Should prospective parents in adoption cases be required to do a parenting course?
</item>
        <item>Are there any risks when adopting a child?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that adopted children should feel especially loved and wanted?
</item>
        <item>Do you it is preferable to adopt or to use artificial reproduction technology?
</item>
        <item>If you had a choice, would you want to be adopted?
</item>
        <item>How would you feel if you found out you were adopted? What would you do?
</item>
        <item>What is the most shocking advertisement you have seen?
</item>
        <item>What is the funniest advertisement you have seen? Describe it.
</item>
        <item>What makes an ad memorable?
</item>
        <item>What are the different types of advertising? (Eg. TV)
</item>
        <item>What types of companies choose each type?
</item>
        <item>Do you buy products because of advertising?
</item>
        <item>Do you find advertising persuasive?
</item>
        <item>Why do you buy one product over another?
</item>
        <item>Should advertisers be allowed to advertise to children?
</item>
        <item>Should alcohol or tobacco companies be allowed to advertise? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of celebrity endorsements?
</item>
        <item>Which celebrities advertise which products?
</item>
        <item>Do favorite or annoying celebrities make you want or not want to buy a product?
</item>
        <item>Should there be advertisement-free zones?
</item>
        <item>Is there truth in advertising?
</item>
        <item>What kind of advertisements attract your attention?
</item>
        <item>Why is it necessary to advertise?
</item>
        <item>Do you think advertising should be allowed to interrupt TV or radio programs? What are the alternatives?
</item>
        <item>What is the best way to advertise to children? Adults? Seniors? etc..
</item>
        <item>Do you think advertising is too expensive?
</item>
        <item>What are some effective adverts you have seen lately (on TV, newspaper, etc)?
</item>
        <item>What are some ineffective adverts you have seen lately?
</item>
        <item>Can you remember an advertising campaign that caught your attention?
</item>
        <item>What are the different methods of advertising?
</item>
        <item>What is the most popular way of advertising?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that the Internet and cable/satellite TV have become more important than national TV for advertising products?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is the best way of discovering the tastes and interests of teenage consumers?
</item>
        <item>Can TV advertising be a force for good?
</item>
        <item>How easy do you think it is to influence children with advertising?
</item>
        <item>What would make an advertisement more interesting?
</item>
        <item>Can you buy something and get something for free in your country?
</item>
        <item>Do people use coupons where you live?
</item>
        <item>What is the most advertised product in your country?
</item>
        <item>What is the best form of advertising?
</item>
        <item>What gets you interested in an advertisement?
</item>
        <item>What is the funniest commercial that you have seen? Describe it.
</item>
        <item>Do you often buy a particular brand when you buy clothes?
</item>
        <item>What brand is the ketchup you or your parents buy?
</item>
        <item>Is it always the same brand? Why do you prefer this brand?
</item>
        <item>What brand is the toothpaste you or your parents buy?
</item>
        <item>Do you think there are too many ads in television? Why/why not?
</item>
        <item>Do you know why some channels have ads and others not? If you do know explain.
</item>
        <item>Do you think there are too many ads in magazines? Why/why not?
</item>
        <item>Think of an ad you think is good or funny and tell about it.
</item>
        <item>What kinds of ads do you like and why? What makes a good ad?
</item>
        <item>Do you think children or young people are easier to influence through ads compared to adults?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it\'s OK to show ads aimed at children on television? Why/ why not?
</item>
        <item>How would you advertise something you wanted to sell?
</item>
        <item>What are the harmful and the beneficial effects of advertising?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that ads create a desire for more and more material possessions?
</item>
        <item>I want to quit smoking. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I won 100,000 dollars and I don\'t know how to spend it. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I gained a lot of weight in last few years. I want to lose at least 10kg. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I have just lost my job. I haven\'t told my husband/wife yet. How should I tell him/her?
</item>
        <item>I found a wallet which had 2,000 dollars in it. How should I spend it?
</item>
        <item>My son doesn\'t want to go to school. He says that his teacher and all other students hate him. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>My child wakes up very often in the middle of the night. He sleeps usually during the day. I haven\'t had any good sleep for weeks. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I have a headache. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I hate working. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I feel sad. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I want to protect the environment but I don\'t know how. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I am always late. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I keep losing my credit card. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I have a red nose. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I am new in this city. I would love to meet some people. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I want to get rich quickly. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I need a car but I don\'t have enough money. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>I want to be a cool man. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>My girlfriend left me. I feel depressed. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>My husband doesn\'t help me with house chores. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever self-published something? What are some good ways to publish your writing independently?
</item>
        <item>If you have a lot of things to get done in one week, how do you manage? What advice would you give someone who is very busy?
</item>
        <item>My girlfriend/boyfriend is seeing another man/woman. I saw a message in his/her mobile phone. What should I do?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is the best age to be?
</item>
        <item>Are young people generally more selfish than their parents and grandparents?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that any of the age limits need changing?
</item>
        <item>Some people think you should give something to society before you have the right to join it.
</item>
        <item>Should people of between 50 and 55 be forced to retire from their jobs in order to make way for younger workers?
</item>
        <item>If people are still able to (and want to) work, should they have to retire when the reach a certain age?
</item>
        <item>Are there many things that the old can teach the young or are they hopelessly out of touch by the time they reach a certain age?
</item>
        <item>Some people say that youth is a state of mind, do you agree?
</item>
        <item>What advice would you give to an older person who wants to feel young?
</item>
        <item>Where do you wish to live when you are old?
</item>
        <item>Should older people spend their money on themselves, or save it for their children to have after they die?
</item>
        <item>Where do you see yourself when you are 70 years old?
</item>
        <item>Where do you wish to live when you are old?
</item>
        <item>Should parents continue to finance their children after the children are 18?
</item>
        <item>Do you prefer to live in the retirement home or live with young people?
</item>
        <item>What is your ideal old age to live to?
</item>
        <item>Are you afraid of getting old?
</item>
        <item>If your parents could no longer care for themselves, would you let them live with you or put them in a nursing home?
</item>
        <item>How do you feel about your parents growing older?
</item>
        <item>How old were you when you went on your first flight?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to travel by airplane?
</item>
        <item>What was the longest flight you have ever taken?
</item>
        <item>Can you sleep during the flight?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen a female pilot?
</item>
        <item>Do you know someone who is afraid of flying in an airplane?
</item>
        <item>What questions should you ask when buying airplane tickets?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever visited an amusement park?
</item>
        <item>What has been the best amusement park you have ever visited? Why?
</item>
        <item>What was your favorite ride or activity? Why?
</item>
        <item>What was your worst ride or activity? Why?
</item>
        <item>If you were to recommend an amusement park, which one would you recommend and why?
</item>
        <item>What rides or activities would you recommend?
</item>
        <item>How regularly do you visit amusement parks?
</item>
        <item>Can you think of an amusement park ride or activity that would be both enjoyable and popular?
</item>
        <item>Are you afraid of going on scary amusement park rides?
</item>
        <item>Do you know of anybody who hurt themselves or died at an amusement park?
</item>
        <item>Even though you may have been terrified by a particular ride, would you go on it again?
</item>
        <item>What are some famous amusement parks near where you live?
</item>
        <item>Do you have any plans to go to an amusement park in the near future?
</item>
        <item>What causes anger?
</item>
        <item>Are there different types of anger?
</item>
        <item>What are various ways people respond to anger?
</item>
        <item>Is anger ever justified? If so, how can we determine whether it is?
</item>
        <item>Is anger ever a good thing? If so, when? Why?
</item>
        <item>Is anger ever a bad thing? If so, when? Why?
</item>
        <item>Are there better and worse ways to respond to one\'s own anger?
</item>
        <item>How do you decide what to do when you get angry?
</item>
        <item>Do you think men and women show their angry differently?
</item>
        <item>What makes you angry?
</item>
        <item>When was the last time you got angry?
</item>
        <item>What do you usually do when you get angry?
</item>
        <item>What are the situations that make you angry?
</item>
        <item>What are the physical effects of getting angry? (e.g blood pressure…)
</item>
        <item>Is getting angry an effective way of dealing with problems?
</item>
        <item>Do you have a pet?
</item>
        <item>Did you grow up with pets in your home?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider getting a pet?
</item>
        <item>If you don\'t have a pet, why not?
</item>
        <item>What are the pros and cons of keeping a pet?
</item>
        <item>What is the best pet to own?
</item>
        <item>What are some animals that live in your country?
</item>
        <item>Are there animal rights groups where you live?
</item>
        <item>Are you afraid of snakes? What is the biggest snake you have seen? Are there any poisonous snakes in your country?
</item>
        <item>Are you frightened of spiders? What do you do if you see one?
</item>
        <item>Can you name some endangered species?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever ridden a horse?
</item>
        <item>Are there birds or squirrels in your neighborhood?
</item>
        <item>Do you know someone who owns an unusual pet?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is acceptable to test cosmetics on animals?
</item>
        <item>How do you feel about the use of animals for medical research?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is okay to eat meat? Do you know any vegetarians?
</item>
        <item>Is there any kind of meat you would not eat?
</item>
        <item>What kind of meats have you eaten?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been to a zoo?
</item>
        <item>Are there laws about hunting in your country?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of hunting? Would you eat an animal that you killed yourself?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of hunting? Would you eat an animal that you killed yourself?
</item>
        <item>Do you think people should buy and wear fur coats?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that animals dream?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been bitten by a dog? Have you been stung by a bee?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been to a farm? What animals did you see there?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been to a horse race?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever eaten rabbit meat? Have you eaten octopus?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen a dog that helps people, such as one to assist a blind person or a policeman?
</item>
        <item>If so, what did you notice about the dog?
</item>
        <item>How do you think that dog was trained?
</item>
        <item>What animals do you think are cute?
</item>
        <item>What animals do you think are ugly?
</item>
        <item>What can children learn by having a pet?
</item>
        <item>What is the largest animal you have ever seen?
</item>
        <item>Why do some people not like pets?
</item>
        <item>What can people learn from animals?
</item>
        <item>Does feeding an animal bring you happiness?
</item>
        <item>Can people be too attached to their pets?
</item>
        <item>Do you think animals have souls?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is right to keep wild animals in captivity all there life
</item>
        <item>Is it morally right to spend a lot of money on pets, rather than helping people in need?
</item>
        <item>Why are pets, not people used for medical research?
</item>
        <item>What is your favorite animal?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had a pet?
</item>
        <item>What kind of pet would you like to have in the future?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been to the zoo? What animals did you see there?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been on a farm? What animals did you see there?
</item>
        <item>Do you think people should wear fur coats?
</item>
        <item>Should animals be kept in a zoo?
</item>
        <item>Do you know any endangered species?
</item>
        <item>Do you consider yourself an animal lover?
</item>
        <item>Do bats help people?
</item>
        <item>What animal is liked to be petted?
</item>
        <item>What kind of animals do humans ride?
</item>
        <item>Are you afraid of snakes?
</item>
        <item>Are you frightened of spiders?
</item>
        <item>Can you ride a horse?
</item>
        <item>Do you ever go bird watching?
</item>
        <item>Do you ever talk to your pet? If so, what do you say?
</item>
        <item>Do you have a cat?
</item>
        <item>Do you have a dog? If so, what\'s your dog\'s name?
</item>
        <item>Do you know anyone who keeps their dog in their house?
</item>
        <item>Do you love your pet?
</item>
        <item>Do you prefer dogs or cats?
</item>
        <item>Do you talk to your pet sometimes?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is right to keep wild animals in a zoo?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that animals dream?
</item>
        <item>Do your pets have special behavior problems?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been bitten by a dog?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been bitten by a snake?
</item>
        <item>Why do people have pets? / Why do people keep pets?
</item>
        <item>Would you recommend that others keep pets similar to yours?
</item>
        <item>In your opinion, why do some people like to have unusual pets?
</item>
        <item>Do you think dogs should be banned or muzzled?
</item>
        <item>Would you want to see aggressive dogs muzzled or banned?
</item>
        <item>What do you think would animals say about humans if they could make a documentary movie about humans?
</item>
        <item>What is a breed?
</item>

        <item>What annoys you about taking trains to work?
</item>
        <item>What annoys you about living where you live now?
</item>
        <item>What annoys you about driving a car?
</item>
        <item>What annoys you most about living at home with your family?
</item>
        <item>Do you think you have habits that annoy other people?
</item>
        <item>Does it annoy you when people kiss in public?
</item>
        <item>Do you get annoyed when someone cuts in front of you when you are waiting in line?
</item>
        <item>What are some new pet peeves you have as a result of recent technology (i.e. cell phone use)?
</item>
        <item>What annoying habits does your best friend have?
</item>
        <item>Does smoking bother you?
</item>
        <item>Do you get annoyed when other people display bad manners? Give some examples.
</item>
        <item>What is the most annoying thing for you?
</item>
        <item>What is the most annoying thing about your partner?
</item>
        <item>Do you annoy people with some of your habits?
</item>
        <item>What is something that your parents do that annoy you?
</item>
        <item>Can annoying someone be a good thing?
</item>
        <item>If something is annoying you, what do you usually do?
</item>
        <item>What are some things that annoy you that don\'t annoy your best friend?
</item>
        <item>How do you change annoying habits
</item>
        <item>What are some things that car drivers do that annoy you?
</item>
        <item>Can you think of some things children do that annoy adults around them?
</item>
        <item>Does it annoy you when people don\'t use the right punctuation?
</item>
        <item>What kind of people annoy you?
</item>
        <item>Who is the most annoying person you know? Why?
</item>
        <item>How do you inform someone they are being annoying
</item>
        <item>Do you think other people find you annoying? Why?
</item>
        <item>Who is the most annoying celebrity? Why?
</item>
        <item>Is there anything about your teacher that annoys you? What will you do about it?
</item>
        <item>Does it annoy you when people don\'t use the right punctuation?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is annoying if people can\'t or don\'t speak your language?
</item>
        <item>Why do people get annoyed?
</item>
        <item>Do bandaids on ladies feet annoy you?
</item>
        <item>What\'s the most annoying thing about your partner?
</item>
        <item>What\'s the most annoying catchphrase or cliche you can think of?
</item>
        <item>Is it worse to be ignorant or annoying?
</item>
        <item>What annoys you about yourself?
</item>
        <item>What do people do on the subway that annoys you?
</item>
        <item>What do people do on the bus that annoys you?
</item>
        <item>What do people do on the street that annoys you?
</item>
        <item>Does it annoy you when people snore?
</item>
        <item>Do you feel bad after you have an argument?
</item>
        <item>What are some reason why people argue?
</item>
        <item>What does your family argue about?
</item>
        <item>How do you avoid arguments?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is best to argue or just walk away? Shy?
</item>
        <item>Do you get along with argumentative people?
</item>
        <item>Are you passionate about your beliefs?
</item>
        <item>Do you ever try to impose your beliefs on others?
</item>
        <item>Do you at times enjoy "playing the devil\'s advocate" (debating for the fun of it)?
</item>
        <item>Do you get along argumentative people?
</item>
        <item>Are you passionate about your beliefs?
</item>
        <item>Would you describe yourself as an argumentative person?
</item>
        <item>What other adjectives would you associate with an argumentative person?
</item>
        <item>In your opinion is being argumentative a positive trait or a flaw?
</item>
        <item>Are you easily persuaded in an argument?
</item>
        <item>Do you ever try to impose your beliefs on others?
</item>
        <item>Do you at times enjoy "playing the devil\'s advocate" (debating for the fun of it)?
</item>
        <item>How do you feel when someone disagrees with everything you have to say?
</item>
        <item>Do have a "butinski" in your family? Do you tend to but in?
</item>
        <item>At work do you often voice your opinions on controversial issues? If so, what kind of reception do get?
</item>
        <item>Do you steer clear of some touchy topics or do you get a kick out of provoking others?
</item>
        <item>How do you grab someone\'s attention when you\'re making a point? What can you do to lose it?
</item>
        <item>Are hand gestures useful in an argument?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it\'s disrespectful to argue with your elders?
</item>
        <item>What do you say when someone is being condescending?
</item>
        <item>Are you a good painter?
</item>
        <item>Can you draw pictures well?
</item>
        <item>Do you believe what art critics say?
</item>
        <item>Do you consider yourself a good artist?
</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy your art class at school?
</item>
        <item>Do you like modern art?
</item>
        <item>Do you like paintings?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to visit art museums?
</item>
        <item>Do you like wood carving?
</item>
        <item>Do you prefer using water colors or oil paint?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is proper to call nude paintings art?
</item>
        <item>Do you think music and dancing are forms of art?
</item>
        <item>Do you think of cartoons and comics as art?
</item>
        <item>Do you visit museums when you go to another city?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been to any famous art museums?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever visited an art museum?
</item>
        <item>What art form do you like best?
</item>
        <item>What famous painters do you know? What are they famous for?
</item>
        <item>What is art?
</item>
        <item>What is the longest time that you have spend on a painting?
</item>
        <item>What is your favorite art web site?
</item>
        <item>What would life be like without art?
</item>
        <item>When was the last time you went to an art museum?
</item>
        <item>Who are some famous artists in your country?
</item>
        <item>Who is a famous potter in your country?
</item>
        <item>Who is the most famous artist in your country? What kind of art does he do?
</item>
        <item>Who is your favorite painter?
</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy taking photographs?
</item>
        <item>What things do you like to photograph?
</item>
        <item>Do you consider photography an art form?
</item>
        <item>Why do artist like to draw women\'s figures?
</item>
        <item>Why do you enjoy art?
</item>
        <item>Why is art important?
</item>
        <item>Why do people become professional artists?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever participated in any art competitions?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been jealous of someone else\'s artwork?
</item>
        <item>Do you find Picasso\'s work astonishing or weird?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever gone to an exhibition?
</item>
        <item>Do you know any art galleries? Are there any in the place where you live?
</item>
        <item>Were you interested in art when you were young?
</item>
        <item>In your opinion, is design an important part of culture?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me the name of a fashion designer you know?
</item>
        <item>Is design a great importance in your daily life?
</item>
        <item>Do you know any art gallery? Is there any in the place where you live?
</item>
        <item>Were you interested in art some years ago? and now?
</item>
        <item>Have you studied any pictorial movement?
</item>
        <item>Has design a great importance in your daily life
</item>
        <item>Is your work figurative or abstract?
</item>
        <item>What is your medium of choice?
</item>
        <item>What influences your work?
</item>
        <item>If you could buy a great work of art, what would it be? (style, title, artist\'s name…)
</item>
        <item>Do you think performance art should be considered art?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of shock art?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen performance art?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen shock art?
</item>
        <item>Does art imitate life?
</item>
        <item>Are movies a form of art?
</item>
        <item>What makes it easy to talk to someone?
</item>
        <item>Tell about your favorite types of conversations to have?
</item>
        <item>Who is the best conversationalist that you have ever met?
</item>
        <item>What is your role in a conversation?
</item>
        <item>What percent of a conversation do you spend talking?
</item>
        <item>What are some good habits you have in conversation?
</item>
        <item>What are some bad traits you have in conversations?
</item>
        <item>Who communicates better: men or women?
 </item>
        <item>Do you like to argue?
</item>
        <item>Do you always want to be right?
</item>
        <item>What topics should you avoid when talking to a stranger?
</item>
        <item>What topics are taboos for your culture?
</item>
        <item>Why do people like to learn bad words in another language?
</item>
        <item>What do people do that drives you crazy in a conversation?
</item>
        <item>How do you feel about talking on the phone? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that some conversations are easier to have on the phone? Face to face?
</item>
        <item>What types of conversations, and why?
</item>
        <item>How do your conversations change after you have been drinking?
</item>
        <item>Is there such a thing as being too honest? Explain.
</item>
        <item>Are there any older people who you have conversations with regularly?
</item>
        <item>If you could have a conversation with any famous living person, who would you talk to?
</item>
        <item>If you could have a conversation with a famous deceased person, who would you talk to?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be a salesman, a teacher, a reporter?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to have a career that requires you to talk to a lot of people? Why?
</item>
        <item>How can you improve your conversation skills? Explain.
</item>
        <item>Do you always carry a bag or purse?
</item>
        <item>What do you usually carry with you?
</item>
        <item>What things do you use every day?
</item>
        <item>What things are important to carry with you?
</item>
        <item>Do you always carry a bank card?
</item>
        <item>Do you always carry money?
</item>
        <item>How much money do you usually carry on you?
</item>
        <item>Do men carry billfolds in your country?
</item>

        <item>Do women carry a purse or handbag in your country?
</item>
        <item>Is it a custom in your country for men to carry or hold the woman\'s purse or bag?
</item>
        <item>Will guys hold their wife\'s and/or girlfriend\'s purse or bag where you live?
</item>
        <item>Do men carry bags or purses in your country
</item>
        <item>What if you see a guy carrying a purse or woman\'s bag, would you think he is gay?
</item>
        <item>What do you think a president would carry on their person?
</item>
        <item>What are essential (necessary) items to take with you when you leave the house?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever played baseball?
</item>
        <item>Do you know the rules of baseball?
</item>
        <item>Do you like baseball?
</item>
        <item>Are you interested in baseball?
</item>
        <item>How many players are on a baseball team?
</item>
        <item>What position do you think is the most difficult?
</item>
        <item>Who is your favorite baseball player? Why do you like him?
</item>
        <item>Does baseball look like a fun game to you?
</item>
        <item>What qualities do you think of baseball player needs to be good?
</item>
        <item>Do they have professional baseball teams in your country?
</item>
        <item>How much does it cost to watch a professional baseball game?
</item>
        <item>Would you rather watch baseball at a stadium or on television?
</item>
        <item>What is your favorite baseball team? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you follow professional baseball?
</item>
        <item>Are there any baseball players from your country playing in the USA?
</item>
        <item>Do you think baseball will ever be a worldwide sport like soccer?
</item>
        <item>What are the differences between baseball in America and baseball in your country?
</item>
        <item>How much does it cost to attend a pro game in your country?
</item>
        <item>What kinds of food are sold at baseball stadiums in your country?
</item>
        <item>Does your country have a minor league?
</item>
        <item>Do you think young players aspire to be a pro in their home country or make it to the American Major Leagues?
</item>
        <item>Are there recreational baseball teams in your country?
</item>
        <item>Do children have easy access to baseball in your country?
</item>
        <item>Do people play softball in your country?
</item>
        <item>Are there women\'s baseball teams in your country?
</item>
        <item>Do you consider baseball to be a slow game?
</item>
        <item>Do you think the playoffs are more exciting than the regular season?
</item>
        <item>Do you think baseball will ever be a worldwide sport like soccer?
</item>
        <item>How does a kid make it to the pros?
</item>
        <item>When was the last time you went to the beach? Where did you go?
</item>
        <item>What do people do at the beach?
</item>
        <item>Can you swim?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been night-swimming?
</item>
        <item>Are there any problems with jellyfish, sharks or stonefish at your local beach?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever played sports on the beach?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever collected seashells?
</item>
        <item>What sort of animals live at the beach?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been fishing on the beach?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been on a sail boat or a row boat?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been on a sail boat or a row boat?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever used a surf board or body board?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to suntan?
</item>
        <item>Do you think sunblock is important?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been to a famous beach?
</item>
        <item>What do you wear to the beach?
</item>
        <item>How do you keep your wallet safe while you are swimming?
</item>
        <item>Is erosion a problem at your local beach?
</item>
        <item>Is pollution a problem at your local beach?
</item>
        <item>Should people be able to own a beach or part of a beach?
</item>
        <item>Why is beachfront land so expensive?
</item>
        <item>Do you prefer a calm sea or do you prefer big waves?
</item>
        <item>Should dogs be allowed on the beach?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of people who swim in the nude?
</item>
        <item>Is there a nude beach near where you live?
</item>
        <item>Which is your favorite beach?
</item>
        <item>Are there life guards at the beaches in your country?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that people should be allowed to drink beer or other drinks with alcohol on the beach?
</item>
        <item>Who do you think is the most beautiful person in your country?
</item>
        <item>Who do you think is the most beautiful person alive today?
</item>
        <item>Who was the most beautiful person in history?
</item>
        <item>Who is the most attractive in your family?
</item>
        <item>Does beauty affect one\'s success in life?
</item>
        <item>Is it better to be physically attractive or intelligent?
</item>
        <item>Is it better to be physically attractive or wealthy?
</item>
        <item>Is beauty related to power?
</item>
        <item>Do people spend too much time and money on beauty?
</item>
        <item>How much time should be spent on making yourself look better each day?
</item>
        <item>Who would you say is beautiful that others maybe wouldn\'t?
</item>
        <item>Do you think people should have cosmetic surgery to enhance their looks?
</item>
        <item>How important is beauty in your daily life?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever noticed anyone ever feeling pressured to be more beautiful?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of the proverb, "beauty is in the eye of the beholder?"
</item>
        <item>What do you think "beauty is skin deep" means?
</item>
        <item>What are some beauty tips that you could share?
</item>
        <item>Do you think people with many tattoos can be beautiful?
</item>
        <item>Do you think people with many piercings can be beautiful?
</item>
        <item>What personality trait is the most important for inner beauty?
</item>
        <item>How do you define beauty, using your own words?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever date someone who was not conventionally attractive?
</item>
        <item>What makes one person more attractive than another?
</item>
        <item>Do you think people from different countries than you see attractive the same way?
</item>
        <item>Is there someone famous that is considered beautiful, that you think is not?
</item>
        <item>Are beauty pageants good or bad?
</item>
        <item>Should children be entered into beauty pageants?
</item>
        <item>Do you think one gender or group worries more about beauty than another?
</item>
        <item>Would you want your children to be beautiful or talented?
</item>
        <item>Would you want your children to be beautiful or talented?
</item>
        <item>What do you think about plastic surgery?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of celebrities who get plastic surgery?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it\'s necessary to have plastic surgery if you are famous in order to be successful?
</item>
        <item>Do you think skin color affects whether a person is regarded as beautiful or not?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that fairer skin makes you more beautiful?
</item>
        <item>What are some advantages of being beautiful?
</item>
        <item>What makes someone beautiful in your country?
</item>
        <item>What do you think "beauty is skin deep" means?
</item>
        <item>How many different adjectives can you think of to describe a beautiful woman or a handsome man
</item>
        <item>What is good behavior? What is bad behavior?
</item>
        <item>Were you well-behaved as a child?
</item>
        <item>What influences you to make good choices?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever not tolerated someone\'s behavior?
</item>
        <item>Would you teach your child to "hit back" at school if somebody hit him?
</item>
        <item>How can we teach our children good behavior? Are words or example more important?
</item>
        <item>Are you influenced by what you see on TV? Or by what you read?
</item>
        <item>Do friends influence you?
</item>
        <item>Can music influence your behavior?
</item>
        <item>Is it important to only watch wholesome TV shows and only read good books?
</item>
        <item>How has the media affected society? Has TV made society better or worse?
</item>
        <item>How does religion influence people\'s behavior?
</item>
        <item>Do you care about the private behavior of a politician?
</item>
        <item>Does the behavior of well-known people, such as celebrities and politicians, affect how average people behave?
</item>
        <item>Does economic status affect people\'s behavior? For example, are people more generous if they have more money?
</item>
        <item>Who do you admire? Do you try to be like this person (or people)?
</item>
        <item>Are there historical figures you admire?
</item>
        <item>Who is affected by your behavior?
</item>
        <item>In what ways have the choices of others affected you?
</item>
        <item>Does your happiness depend on the behavior of others?
</item>
        <item>Should you always be on your best behavior?
</item>
        <item>Will we be judged for our behavior? Do you believe in a God who punishes bad people and rewards good people?
</item>
        <item>Does it always pay to be good?
</item>
        <item>How do you act when you are happy? Do you like being around happy people?
</item>
        <item>Should people act on their feelings? If you are in a bad mood, can people around you tell?
</item>
        <item>Do you believe we have a moral obligation to act happy, even if we do not feel happy?
</item>
        <item>Is it possible to change one\'s behavior?
</item>
        <item>Have you changed anything about your behavior?
</item>
        <item>Do you set goals to improve yourself?
</item>
        <item>What behaviors are expected from children towards their parents?
</item>
        <item>Do the clothes you wear affect your behavior? Should school teachers wear casual clothes?
</item>
        <item>What behaviors are expected from university and college students?
</item>
        <item>Should corporal punishment be illegal?
</item>
        <item>Are bad people bad because of circumstances or choices? What about good people?
</item>
        <item>Do you think there is such a thing as an evil person, or just a sick person?
</item>
        <item>Can bad behavior lead to crime?
</item>
        <item>Should parents be held responsible for their children\'s behavior?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you saw somebody else\'s child behaving badly in public?
</item>
        <item>Should some parent give medicine to their children to calm them down?
</item>
        <item>Can you think of a behavior that is \'good\' behavior in one culture and a \'bad\' behavior in another culture?
</item>
        <item>How would you behave in a hospital?
</item>
        <item>What is the strangest thing you have ever done?
</item>
        <item>Should children be punished in public?
</item>
        <item>What kind of punishment do you think is the most effective ?
</item>
        <item>What does "misbehavior" mean?
</item>
        <item>What can we do to prevent or discourage it
</item>
        <item>Is there a behavior considered a \'good\' behavior in one culture and a \'bad\'
</item>
        <item>behavior in another culture? If yes, give examples.
</item>
        <item>Can we teach our children good behavior?
</item>
        <item>How can we teach our children good behavior?
</item>
        <item>How do children acquire good behavior?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if your child behaves badly in public?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you saw somebody else\'s child behaves badly in public?
</item>
        <item>Would you spank (To slap on the buttocks with a flat object or with the open hand, as for punishment) your child for bad behavior?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you saw somebody spanking their child behaves for bad behavior?
</item>
        <item>What should you do with a child who has very bad behavior?
</item>
        <item>Would you teach your child to "hit back" at school if somebody hits them?
</item>
        <item>How should we punish children who commit crimes?
</item>
        <item>What behavior is not acceptable among friends?
</item>
        <item>How should movie stars behave in public?
</item>
        <item>Is it OK to show negative types of behavior when you are angry?
</item>
        <item>What behaviors make you feel good?
</item>
        <item>What behaviors make you feel angry?
</item>
        <item>Should children be encouraged to ask questions in class?
</item>
        <item>How can teachers stop "bullying" at school?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever got embarrassed by your friend\'s/girlfriend\'s/husband\'s misbehavior?
</item>
        <item>What is the right behavior to use in a job interview?
</item>
        <item>How should you behave when you see someone you don\'t like?
</item>
        <item>What is good behavior?
</item>
        <item>What is the right behavior to use in a restaurant?
</item>
        <item>Can you think of a behavior that is \'good\' behavior in one culture and a \'bad\' behavior in another culture?
</item>
        <item>Can we teach our children good behavior?
</item>
        <item>How can we teach our children good behavior?
</item>
        <item>How do children acquire good behavior?
</item>
        <item>Would you spank your child for bad behavior?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you saw somebody spanking their child for bad behavior?
</item>
        <item>Is it acceptable for parents to spank their children?
</item>
        <item>How are birthdays celebrated in your country?
</item>
        <item>What are some birthday traditions you know of from other countries?
</item>
        <item>How do you like to celebrate your birthday?
</item>
        <item>What is your best birthday memory?
        </item>
        <item>What is your worst birthday memory?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had a surprise birthday party for yourself or someone else?
</item>
        <item>What is the best birthday gift you have ever received?
</item>
        <item>What is the worst birthday gift you have ever received?
</item>
        <item>What are some things you like to do for your birthday?
</item>
        <item>Did your parents give you birthday parties when you were a child?
</item>
        <item>In your opinion, What is the best time of year to have a birthday?
</item>
        <item>How do people you know celebrate turning 40?
</item>
        <item>Do you think getting older (40, 50, 60) is depressing for people, or a happy occasion?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is the best age?
</item>
        <item>Do you like going to work on your birthday?
</item>
        <item>Did you like going to school on your birthday when you were a child?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had a surprise party?
</item>
        <item>Whose birthday do you always remember?
</item>
        <item>Among your close friends and relatives, whose birthday is coming up next?
</item>
        <item>About how many birthday gifts or cards do you send or give to people each year?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever forgotten someone\'s birthday that you should have remembered?
</item>
        <item>Do you know any famous people\'s birthdays? (Are any the same as yours?)
</item>
        <item>Do you know of any big events that happened the year you were born?
</item>
        <item>What is the best birthday gift you have ever received?
</item>
        <item>What is the best birthday gift you have ever given?
</item>
        <item>What is the worst birthday gift you have ever received?
</item>
        <item>What is the worst birthday gift you have ever given?
</item>
        <item>Would you rather celebrate your birthday with just your relatives or just your friends?
</item>
        <item>Do you remember what gifts you received on your last birthday?
</item>
        <item>Do you remember what gifts you received on your last birthday?
</item>
        <item>What would you like to get most for your birthday this year?
</item>
        <item>Is the cost of a present important to you?
</item>
        <item>What kind of gift do you usually prepare for your friend\'s birthday?
</item>
        <item>Which is a better present, a well-chosen gift or money?
</item>
        <item>Are birthdays really important?
</item>
        <item>How do you celebrate your birthday?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think body language is important?
</item>
        <item>How do you use body language in your daily life?
</item>
        <item>How does body language help you to communicate?
</item>
        <item>What "new" body language have you seen since coming to your new country? did those actions confuse you?
</item>
        <item>How does eye contact differ from your native country to your new one?
</item>
        <item>How can you misinterpret someone\'s body language?
</item>
        <item>Do you try to use body language when you communicate in English?
</item>
        <item>What is the longest book you have ever read?
</item>
        <item>What is the funniest book you have ever read?
</item>
        <item>How many books have you read in your life?
</item>
        <item>Is there a time in your life when you read all the time?
</item>
        <item>How many hours do you spend reading in a week?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been to a book signing or met an author?
</item>
        <item>Do you have any ideas for a story for you to write?
</item>
        <item>Do you read books based on recommendations?
</item>
        <item>What are some of the books that were recommended to you?
</item>
        <item>How do you choose the books you are going to read?
</item>
        <item>Most people say the book is better than the movie. Is this true for you?
</item>
        <item>Did you enjoy reading books in school?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that it is more valuable to read a book than to watch television?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that the internet and television will eventually make books obsolete?
</item>
        <item>Where from do you get inspiration for growth?
</item>
        <item>How often do you travel abroad?
</item>
        <item>What one thing can transform business to a higher level?
</item>
        <item>What do you feel about growth of your company?
</item>
        <item>How old were you when you first learned to drive?
</item>
        <item>Can you drive a car?
</item>
        <item>Can you drive a manual shift car?
</item>
        <item>Do you have a car? If so, what kind of car do you have?</item>
        <item>What are the advantages of owning a car?
</item>
        <item>What are the disadvantages of owning a car?
</item>
        <item>Are you a good driver?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been in a car accident?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been pulled over by the police?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever driven a car in a foreign country?
</item>
        <item>Are the drivers in your area where you live good drivers?
</item>
        <item>Do you know anything about repairing or maintaining a car?
</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy repairing cars?
</item>
        <item>Do you prefer driving or riding public transportation?
</item>
        <item>What kind of car do you prefer?
</item>
        <item>Do you like drive at night?
        </item>
        <item>Do you think cars should be banned from city centers?
</item>
        <item>What side of the road do you drive in your country?
</item>
        <item>Is drunk driving a problem in your country?
</item>
        <item>What kind of laws does your country have about drunk driving?
</item>
        <item>What kind of laws does your country have about drunk driving?
</item>
        <item>What is the penalty for drunk driving in your country?
</item>
        <item>Who taught you to drive?
</item>
        <item>How long did it take you to learn to drive?
</item>
        <item>What is the longest trip you have ever taken by car?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever broken down and been stranded on the side of the road?
</item>
        <item>How do American drivers compare to drivers in your country?
</item>
        <item>What are the speed limits in your country?
</item>
        <item>On what occasions do you honk your car horn?
</item>
        <item>Is it acceptable to honk in your country
</item>
        <item>Are men better drivers than women?
</item>
        <item>Are women better drivers than men?
</item>
        <item>At what age can you get a licence in your country?
</item>
        <item>Do you think the age for driving should be raised or lowered?
</item>
        <item>Do you think driving lessons should be provided by high schools?
</item>
        <item>Should new drivers have a period of accompanied driving?
</item>
        <item>What can we tell or imagine about a person by looking at the car they drive?
</item>
        <item>What are the laws about seat belts in your country?
</item>
        <item>What are the advantages and disadvantages of air conditioning?
</item>
        <item>Do you allow passengers to eat inside your car?
</item>
        <item>What are the advantages/disadvantages of buying a second-hand car?
</item>
        <item>Do you wash your car yourself or do you have it washed?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that there is a relation between global warming and cars?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen a "hybrid" car?
</item>
        <item>What do you know about "hybrid" cars?
</item>
        <item>Do you really think that car manufacturers are interested in global warming?
</item>
        <item>How often do you need to get your car repaired?
        </item>
        <item>On what occasions do you honk your car horn?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever bribed a policeman in your country after he pulled you over?
</item>
        <item>How are the traffic laws in your country?
</item>
        <item>Do most people follow the rules of the road?
</item>
        <item>What should be done in order to prevent traffic congestion in your city?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen a celebrity in person? What did you do?
</item>
        <item>Which celebrity would you like to meet? What would you do if you could spend a day with this person?
</item>
        <item>Do you think famous people have the right to have a private life?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it\'s moral to sell your private life to the media?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of the paparazzi?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think there is such a high demand for gossip magazines and gossip TV programs?
</item>
        <item>What are the pros and cons of being a celebrity?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of fans and fan-clubs ?
</item>
        <item>Did you have any heroes when you were a teenager?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think adolescents need to have heroes?
</item>
        <item>Do you think being a celebrity automatically means the person is intelligent?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that there are times when the common man has an edge over a celebrity?
</item>
        <item>If you could influence people like a celebrity does, how would you use it for the benefit of the planet?
</item>
        <item>Which celebrity do you most admire and why ?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be famous ? Why or why not ?
</item>
        <item>Do you think there is a relationship between beauty and celebrity ?
</item>
        <item>Can you name some famous people?
</item>
        <item>Do you know someone famous?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be famous? Why?
</item>
        <item>Are famous people happy?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be a celebrity?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be a celebrity? Why would you be famous?
</item>
        <item>If you were a celebrity, would you take advantage of it to date some fans?
</item>
        <item>Should celebrities be role models?
</item>
        <item>Do you think being a celebrity automatically means the person is intelligent? Why? Why not?
</item>
        <item>Do you think celebrities write their own music?
</item>
        <item>Can you give some examples of when the common man has an edge over a celebrity?
</item>
        <item>Have you made any recent changes in your life?
</item>
        <item>Do you ever get the urge to refurnish your whole house?
</item>
        <item>Do you rearrange the furniture in your house often?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to rearrange your room or living-room?
</item>
        <item>Do you think change is important in people\'s life?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is possible for a cold hearted person to change?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that it is easy to mend our old ways?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is easy to keep up with the times?
</item>
        <item>If you could change anything in your life, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>What is the most difficult change you have ever had to make?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever decided to get a tattoo?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever cut your hair really short?
</item>
        <item>What was the craziest change in appearance you have ever made?
</item>
        <item>What was the last major change you made in your life?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever decided to change the group that you usually hang out (spend time) with?
</item>
        <item>What is one thing that you think you will never change about yourself?
</item>
        <item>What is one thing you have tried to change, but couldn\'t?
</item>
        <item>If you won a million dollars what things would you change about your life?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever converted (changed) over to a different religion?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever changed over to a different political party.
</item>
        <item>Have you ever dumped a boyfriend or girlfriend? Was the change difficult?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever said no to a friend?
</item>
        <item>Have you lost a pet, or has a person ever passed away on you?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever quit your job?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had to change the way you speak, or the way you act? Why?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever decided to change the way you dress? If so, why?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever decided to change the way you eat, or your form of exercise?
</item>
        <item>What is your definition of cheating?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever cheated?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think that people cheat?
        </item>
        <item>Have you ever cheated in an exam?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been caught cheating on an exam?
</item>
        <item>If you had a chance to cheat now, would you take it?
</item>
        <item>In what situations do people usually cheat?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been cheated on by somebody else?
</item>
        <item>Describe a time when you cheated and it helped you.
</item>
        <item>Do you think if people stopped cheating the world would be a better place?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of people who cheat in their relationships?
</item>
        <item>What do you think can be done to prevent cheating?
</item>
        <item>What are some things you can do to prevent cheating?
</item>
        <item>What would you do it you saw someone cheating at something.
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had children?
</item>
        <item>Did you have a happy childhood?
</item>
        <item>What did you like to do when you were a child?
</item>
        <item>Where were you born?
</item>
        <item>How old were you when you learned to ride a bicycle?
</item>
        <item>Who was your favorite teacher? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you remember anything about your personality when a child?
</item>
        <item>What were some embarrassing situations when you were a child?
</item>
        <item>Were you a good student?
</item>
        <item>What did you like about school?
</item>
        <item>What didn\'t you like about school?
</item>
        <item>Who was your best friend?
</item>
        <item>When you were a child, what did you want to grow up to be? Did you want to be a mother or father? A firefighter? A doctor? A scientist?
</item>
        <item>Can you remember specific things from your childhood clearly?
</item>
        <item>What was your favorite toy when you were a child?
</item>
        <item>What was your worst punishment as a child?
</item>
        <item>How are you similar to your parents? How are you different?
</item>
        <item>Do you think children today eat too much fast food and don\'t play enough sports?
</item>
        <item>Did you have any nickname? Tell us about it.
</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy being around children?
</item>
        <item>When you were a child, what did you want to be when you grew up?
</item>
        <item>What are the positive or negative things about being a child?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that children are different today from the time when you were child? Or from 50 years ago? 100 years ago?
</item>
        <item>What is most annoying or amazing thing about children?
</item>
        <item>What is the most important thing that we need to teach children?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that children are naturally good? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>What were some important experiences that you had when you were child which shaped you as a person?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think children commit violent crimes?
</item>
        <item>Do you think children are more violent today than they used to be? Why?
</item>
        <item>What was your favorite game when you were a child?
</item>
        <item>Do we have to answer children\'s questions even if they are inappropriate ones?
</item>
        <item>What are the most important lessons to teach young children at home? Older children?
</item>
        <item>Is childhood the best time of life?
</item>
        <item>Who raised you? Your parents or grandparents or another family member?
</item>
        <item>Are you close to your parents? Do you get along well with your parents?
</item>
        <item>What did your family like to do together when you were a child?
</item>
        <item>What are your fondest childhood memories?
</item>
        <item>What are your earliest childhood memories?
</item>
        <item>What were your favorite games as a child?
</item>
        <item>How did you play as a child?
</item>
        <item>Who was your best childhood friend?
</item>
        <item>What was the most important lesson your parents taught you?
</item>
        <item>Should children be paid for household chores?
</item>
        <item>Can you remember doing anything that got you into trouble? What was it? How were you punished?
</item>
        <item>Should children be spanked? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Do you think children today are under more pressure?
</item>
        <item>Do you think parents today have less time for their children?
</item>
        <item>Do you think video games are a bad influence on children?
</item>
        <item>Do you think children watch too much television?
</item>
        <item>Do we have a responsibility to correct children when their parents aren\'t around and they are misbehaving?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is important for children to learn English and their family\'s native language? Why?
</item>
        <item>How do you think children can learn through play ?
</item>
        <item>What are basic children\'s rights?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell when a child is being honest or trying to get away from something? How?
</item>
        <item>Did you have any accidents at home as a child? If yes, what happened?
</item>
        <item>What\'s something children do that you\'d like to be able to do it too?
</item>
        <item>What\'s the cutest thing you think children do?
</item>
        <item>What kind of games do you like to play these days with children?
</item>
        <item>Is there a best time to have children?
</item>
        <item>How does your family decide who does various chores around the house?
</item>
        <item>Can you name some chores that need to be done everyday?
</item>
        <item>What chores are your responsibility?
</item>
        <item>Which chores do you not like to do.
</item>
        <item>How do you decide on your children\'s chores?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to clean up your room?
</item>
        <item>Do you wash the dishes in your house?
</item>
        <item>Do you wash clothes for your family?
</item>
        <item>Do you do the ironing the clothes?
</item>
        <item>What are some chores you do outside your house?
</item>
        <item>Can you think of some dangerous chores that you can\'t do?
</item>
        <item>If you could buy only one of this two things, would you choose a dishwasher or a washing machine?
</item>
        <item>How long do you think you could live without a maid or someone to help you in the house?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to go to the supermarket?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had an empty fridge for a long time only because you were too lazy to go grocery shopping?
</item>
        <item>What kind of products does your family buy on the Internet?
</item>
        <item>If you could have a robot to do all your chores, what would you choose for it to do?
</item>
        <item>What chores do you do that your parents didn\'t have to do when they were growing up?
</item>
        <item>What are some chores that your parents have to do around the house?
</item>
        <item>Do your grandparents help with chores?
</item>
        <item>Why do you like living in the city?
</item>
        <item>What are some of the advantages of living in a city?
</item>
        <item>Do you know the neighbors who live near you?
</item>
        <item>What\'s your favorite city? Why?
</item>
        <item>What city do you live in?
</item>
        <item>What aspects of life in the city would you complain about?
</item>
        <item>What do you think should be done to improve living condition in cities?
</item>
        <item>What are some differences between living in the city and living in the country?
</item>
        <item>What size city is best to live in? Why?
</item>
        <item>What are the names of two big cities in Europe?
</item>
        <item>What are the names of two small cities in Europe?
</item>
        <item>Would you prefer to live in a really old historical city, or a really new modern city?
</item>
        <item>If you had grown up in a different city, how would your life have been different?
</item>
        <item>Did you grow up in the city or in the country?
</item>
        <item>Would you enjoy designing a new city ?
</item>
        <item>Do you walk alone at night in your home city?
</item>
        <item>Would you want to be the mayor of your city?
</item>
        <item>Would you want to be a member of the city council of your city?
</item>
        <item>What monuments of your city do you consider the most impressive? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you like modern cosmopolitan architecture?
</item>
        <item>How would you describe the architecture of your city?
</item>
        <item>Which cities do you feel safe in?
</item>
        <item>Which cities have the best bus services/taxis/metro?
</item>
        <item>How can we make our cities safer places to live?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that each city should have their own laws or could all cities share the same general laws?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you were in charge of a city? How would you improve it?
</item>
        <item>Do you know if your city has a disaster plan for earthquakes, fires, tsunamis, etc?
</item>
        <item>Do all the cities in your country or the U.S. have the same educational system?
</item>
        <item>Can you suggest some good tourist sites to visit in your city?
</item>
        <item>Does your city have a professional or semi-professional sports team?
</item>
        <item>What are you doing to reduce the amount of pollution in your city?
</item>
        <item>If you had grown up in a different city, how would your life have been different?
</item>
        <item>Would you enjoy designing a new city?
</item>
        <item>Can you name two cities in twenty different countries around the world?
</item>
        <item>Do you think some cities are becoming too large? Why?
</item>
        <item>What are some tourist attractions in your city?
</item>
        <item>What are some historical places in your city? Have you visited them?
</item>
        <item>What\'s the most prestigious university in your city?
</item>
        <item>What are the major problems in your city?
</item>
        <item>Where\'s the trendiest area in your city? Do you enjoy going there?
</item>
        <item>who are some famous personalities from your city?
</item>
        <item>What would you do to improve some aspects of your city?
</item>
        <item>Which city\'s sports team do you cheer for?
</item>
        <item>Is your city very cosmopolitan?
</item>
        <item>What are some cosmopolitan cities around the world
</item>
        <item>What is the most important part of a city?
</item>
        <item>Who is the local government head in your city?
</item>
        <item>Which cities would you like to visit in your home country?
</item>
        <item>Which cities would you like to visit around the world?
</item>
        <item>What do you like about your classroom?
</item>
        <item>Do you think the teacher should assign seats to students?
</item>
        <item>What kind of classroom setting is the best for you?
</item>
        <item>What are five things you like about your classroom?
</item>
        <item>What are five things you don\'t like about your classroom?
</item>
        <item>What are five things you would like to change in your classroom?
</item>
        <item>What equipment for teaching is in your classroom?
</item>
        <item>Do you like classroom with fixed desks or movable desks? Why?
</item>
        <item>How much time a day do you spend in a classroom?
</item>
        <item>How much time a day do you spend in a classroom looking out the window?
</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy changing classrooms for different classes?
</item>
        <item>What is the ideal seating plan or arrangement in a classroom?
</item>
        <item>Is there any air conditioning in your classroom?
</item>
        <item>Is your classroom a nice place to study?
</item>
        <item>Do you like the location of your desk in your classroom?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that smart students always sit down in front?
</item>
        <item>What are the advantages of cloning?
</item>
        <item>What are the disadvantages of cloning?
</item>
        <item>Do you think animals should be cloned?
</item>
        <item>Do you think vegetables should be modified?
</item>
        <item>What are the ethical concerns about cloning?
</item>
        <item>Are you against or in favor of cloning? Why?
</item>
        <item>How does cloning affect our lives?
</item>
        <item>Can you name some animals that have been cloned?
</item>
        <item>What do you think about eating the meat from cloned animals?
</item>
        <item>About how much money do you spend on clothes a year?
</item>
        <item>Do you like shopping for new clothes?
</item>
        <item>Do you often buy new clothes?
</item>
        <item>Do you prefer to go shopping or just browse? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you think men should be allowed to wear skirts?
</item>
        <item>What piece of clothing do you spend your money on the most? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you read fashion magazines?
</item>
        <item>Do you sometimes wear a hat?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is important to wear fashionable clothes?
</item>
        <item>Do you wear jewelry?
</item>
        <item>Do you wear the same color clothes now that you wore ten years ago?
</item>
        <item>Do you wear the same size clothes this year as you wore last year?
</item>
        <item>Do you think people feel different when they wear different clothes?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever made your own clothes?
</item>
        <item>How many pairs of gloves do you have?
</item>
        <item>What are some of the strangest fashions you have seen?
</item>
        <item>What colors do you think look good on you?
</item>
        <item>What colors do you think look good on your mother?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of body piercing?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of people who dye their hair green?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of women who wear high heel shoes?
</item>
        <item>What fashions that you see today do you think will be out of fashion within two years?
</item>
        <item>What kind of clothes are in fashion now?
</item>
        <item>What kind of clothes do you usually wear?
</item>
        <item>What\'s the most expensive piece of clothing you have ever bought?
</item>
        <item>What\'s your favorite color for shoes?
</item>
        <item>When was the last time you got dressed up?
</item>
        <item>Where are some good stores to buy clothes in this area?
</item>
        <item>Where do you usually buy clothes?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be a fashion model?
</item>
        <item>Do you like comics?
</item>
        <item>Have you watched any anime?
        </item>
        <item>How are comics different from one country to another?
</item>
        <item>How have comics changed over time?
</item>
        <item>How many comics do you read a week?
</item>
        <item>How often do you read comics?
</item>
        <item>Should comics have a rating system like the movies (G, PG, R)?
</item>
        <item>What comics have you read in English?
</item>
        <item>What can you learn from comics?
</item>
        <item>What is more important to you, the story or the pictures?
</item>
        <item>If you could have one superpower what would it be?
</item>
        <item>What is the best superpower to have?
</item>
        <item>What are some complaints that some parents have about comic books?
</item>
        <item>Why do people like to read comic books?
</item>
        <item>How do you commute to your school or your place of work?
</item>
        <item>How far do you travel and how long does it take you?
</item>
        <item>How do you travel? Is it expensive? Is it tiring?
</item>
        <item>What are some of the reasons why people commute?
</item>
        <item>Would you rather work in a nearer place?
</item>
        <item>If you work far from your house, why have you chosen to commute a long way to work?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever travel between countries or states in order to keep a better job? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>In your viewpoint, what are the advantages and disadvantages of commuting?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to live abroad? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Are there certain professions which require commuting?
</item>
        <item>Would you give up your job if you had to commute frequently?
</item>
        <item>Would you accept a job that requires commuting two hours a day one way?
</item>
        <item>When is it appropriate to complain in a restaurant?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of the saying, "The customer is always right."?
</item>
        <item>What do you say to someone to complain about bad service in a store or restaurant?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever gotten angry at a worker in a store or a restaurant?
</item>
        <item>What are some reasons why we might need to complain in a store or restaurant?
</item>
        <item>What are some reasons why you would not complain about bad service?
</item>
        <item>Do you prefer to make a complaint over the telephone or in person?
</item>
        <item>Is it common in your country to complain about bad service?
</item>
        <item>Do you know any computer programming languages?
</item>
        <item>Do you want a more powerful computer? If so, what computer do you want?
</item>
        <item>Does your family have a computer?
</item>
        <item>How fast can you type?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever taken a course at school where you used a computer?
</item>
        <item>How do you study English with your computer?
</item>
        <item>What is conflict?
</item>
        <item>When you see the word "conflict", what do you think of?
</item>
        <item>What causes conflict?
</item>
        <item>How can conflicts be resolved?
</item>
        <item>What would you consider to be a constructive approach to conflict?
</item>
        <item>What would you consider to be a destructive approach to conflict?
</item>
        <item>Does there have to be a winner and a loser of a conflict?
</item>
        <item>What happens to people who are involved in conflicts?
</item>
        <item>What conflicts are going on around the world?
</item>
        <item>What conflicts exist in your life?
</item>
        <item>How do you deal with conflicts?
</item>
        <item>Can violent conflicts be solved with violence?
</item>
        <item>How can the world be peaceful when other countries are not trying to bring peace?
</item>
        <item>Can conflicts at work place affect the efficiency of one\'s work?
</item>
        <item>Is it possible to avoid conflicts?
</item>
        <item>What strategies do you know to solve conflicts in the family?
</item>
        <item>Can corruption be a good thing?
</item>
        <item>What can you do about corruption in your country?
</item>
        <item>Can corruption be a good thing in some societies?
</item>
        <item>Do you think corrupt police officers are natural-born criminals?
</item>
        <item>Do you know a corruption case?
</item>
        <item>Is corruption ever justifiable?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever received a bribe?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever bribed someone?
</item>
        <item>What country would you like to visit?
</item>
        <item>What country would you like to live in and why?
</item>
        <item>What country would you like to work in?
</item>
        <item>What country has the most interesting customs?
</item>
        <item>What country would be fun to work in?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to work in a tropical country?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to work in Antarctica?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to live where there is always snow?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to live where there is desert and hot weather?
</item>
        <item>What countries in Europe have you visited?
</item>
        <item>What countries would you not like to visit and why?
</item>
        <item>What country in Asia would be a great place to live?
</item>
        <item>Is your country the best place for you to live?
</item>
        <item>What is special about your country?
</item>
        <item>What festivals and feasts does your country have?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to go and live in another country?
</item>
        <item>What countries would you like to travel to for a vacation?
</item>
        <item>How would you travel to see your country?
</item>
        <item>How would you travel the world?
</item>
        <item>What countries would you travel to if you were to do a world trip?
</item>
        <item>Which country gets the most snowfall and why?
</item>
        <item>What country/ countries neighbor (neighbor) your country?
</item>
        <item>What are some similarities and differences between your neighboring country and your country?
</item>
        <item>What is creativity?
</item>
        <item>Do you consider yourself a creative person? Why?
</item>
        <item>What is something creative that you have done?
</item>
        <item>Is creativity a good thing? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>What are some ways that a person can be creative?
</item>
        <item>Is taking a risk part of creativity?
</item>
        <item>Do you often ask question the way things work?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to improve things?
</item>
        <item>What are some creative ways to entertain children?
</item>
        <item>Can you think of a device that would make people\'s life easier?
</item>
        <item>How does self-confidence affect a person\'s creativity?
</item>
        <item>How does early exposure to diverse stimuli, and his involvement in creative activities affect a child\'s future creativity?
</item>
        <item>Does the education system in your country encourage creativity? How?
</item>
        <item>Do you think creativity comes with time and thought or you are born with creative talent?
</item>
        <item>What creative activities did you do as a child?
</item>
        <item>What are some incentives for creative people in the workplace?
</item>
        <item>What is a creative business that you would like to start?
</item>
        <item>Who are some of history\'s most creative people?
</item>
        <item>In which professional field do you think people are most creative? e.g science
</item>
        <item>Do you often answer questions by explaining how things work?
</item>
        <item>Can you think of devices that would make people\'s life easier?
</item>
        <item>Are some parts of this city considered more dangerous than others? Which parts?
</item>
        <item>Are there any places you are afraid to visit because of the high crime rate? If so, where?
</item>
        <item>Are there problems with drugs where you live?
</item>
        <item>Are you apprehensive about walking outside after dark?
</item>
        <item>Do you always lock your house? How about your car?
</item>
        <item>Do you believe that public executions would deter crime? If so, how?
</item>
        <item>Do you drink and drive?
</item>
        <item>Do you know anyone who has been mugged?
</item>
        <item>Do you know someone who has been a victim of a violent crime?
</item>
        <item>Do you think abortion is a crime?
</item>
        <item>Do you think gun control is a good idea? Explain.
</item>
        <item>Do you think people who use illegal drugs should be put in jail?
</item>
        <item>Do you think police TV dramas are realistic?
</item>
        <item>Do you think policeman should be allowed to carry guns?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that capital punishment is a good idea? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that punishment for violent crimes should be the same for juveniles and adults? Why/why not?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that the death penalty would prevent crime in your country? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that the legalization of narcotics would decrease the crime rate?
</item>
        <item>Do you think there are any legal drugs that should be illegal?
</item>
        <item>Do you think there is a link between drugs and crime?
</item>
        <item>Do you think prostitution is a crime?
</item>
        <item>Do you think there will be more or less crime in the future?
</item>
        <item>Does prison help rehabilitate criminals? Should it?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been the victim of a crime? How about others in your family?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever done anything illegal? If so, what did you do?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had anything stolen?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen a crime?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever stolen anything?
</item>
        <item>How can you prevent things from being stolen?
</item>
        <item>If a person steals a loaf of bread because he needs to feed his starving family, should he be punished?
</item>
        <item>Is child abuse a problem in your country?
</item>
        <item>Is drunk driving a crime where you live? If so, what is the punishment?
</item>
        <item>Is it ever O.K. to break the law? If so, when?
</item>
        <item>Is prison an effective punishment? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Is there a problem with organized crime and/or gangs where you live?
</item>
        <item>Is your hometown considered safe?
</item>
        <item>Under what situations would you think of committing a crime?
</item>
        <item>What are some things people can do to protect themselves from crime?
</item>
        <item>What are some things that are legal that you personally think should be illegal?
</item>
        <item>What crimes do you think will decrease in the future?
</item>
        <item>What crimes do you think will increase in the future?
</item>
        <item>What crimes have you heard about recently in the news?
</item>
        <item>Under what situations would you think of committing a crime?
</item>
        <item>What are some things people can do to protect themselves from crime?
</item>
        <item>What are some things that are legal that you personally think should be illegal?
</item>
        <item>What crimes do you think will decrease in the future?
</item>
        <item>What crimes do you think will increase in the future?
</item>
        <item>What crimes have you heard about recently in the news?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is the worst crime a person could commit? Why?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of the death penalty?
</item>
        <item>What is the punishment for murder in your country?
</item>
        <item>What is the punishment for stealing in your country?
</item>
        <item>What kinds of crime are most common in your country? What are the penalties for these crimes?
</item>
        <item>What kinds of crimes are increasing?
</item>
        <item>What kinds of crimes do you think can be prevented? How?
</item>
        <item>What makes some people become criminals? Is it poverty, upbringing, lack of education, unemployment or something else?
</item>
        <item>What weapons do police carry in this country? How about your home country?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you heard a burglar in your house?
</item>
        <item>What\'s your opinion about the death penalty?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think people steal things?
</item>
        <item>Why do people commit crimes?
</item>
        <item>What can be done about gun/knife violence?
</item>
        <item>Do you think your city is a dangerous place to live in?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever witnessed a crime? If "yes" tell us about it.
</item>
        <item>Have you ever witnessed acts of vandalism?
</item>
        <item>Do you think graffiti is vandalism or art?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been robbed?
</item>
        <item>Do you agree that terrorism is the evil of the 21st century?
</item>
        <item>Is bribery a crime?
</item>
        <item>What are some things that define a culture? For example, music, language, …
</item>
        <item>What do you think is interesting about your culture?
</item>
        <item>Do you know much about your own culture?
</item>
        <item>When people from other countries think about your culture, what do they usually think of?
</item>
        <item>In your culture is it polite to be straightforward and direct when you talk to someone?
</item>
        <item>What has surprised you when you\'ve met people from other countries?
</item>
        <item>Have you looked at Internet pages from a different culture? If so, how were they different from those of your own culture?
</item>
        <item>What do you like about your culture?
</item>
        <item>What don\'t you like about your culture?
</item>
        <item>How do young people in your culture behave differently from older people?
</item>
        <item>How do young people in your culture behave differently from people in this culture?
</item>
        <item>Are there many people of different cultures in your country? Are you friends with any?
</item>
        <item>How are your language teachers who are not from your country different from your other teachers?
</item>
        <item>Who in your culture do you admire most?
</item>
        <item>What your culture are you most proud about?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think culture is important?
</item>
        <item>If you could change one thing about your culture, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider marrying or dating someone from another culture?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider living permanently in a country other than your home country? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>What does it mean to be polite in your culture?
</item>
        <item>What is considered rude in your culture?
</item>
        <item>If a group of people just came to your country from overseas, what advice would you give them?
</item>
        <item>What other cultures have you met people from?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is important when visiting another culture?
</item>
        <item>Do you think "when in Rome, do as the Romans do" is always good advice? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been in a situation where you felt you had to "do as the Romans do"?
</item>
        <item>What culture besides your own do you admire and why?
</item>
        <item>If aliens visited your country, what might surprise them?
</item>
        <item>Do you pray before each meal?
</item>
        <item>How do you feel when you leave your home culture and enter into a completely new culture?
</item>
        <item>What is the best/most important thing your culture has given to the world?
</item>
        <item>What is the best/most important thing your culture/country has adopted from another culture?
</item>
        <item>If you could choose three aspects of your culture to put in a "time box" for the future, what would you put in it?
</item>
        <item>What is culture shock?
</item>
        <item>Have you been in the midst of danger before?
</item>
        <item>What do you do when you feel someone might be following you?
</item>
        <item>If you are in danger, what should you do?
</item>
        <item>If your life was in danger, who would you call and why?
</item>
        <item>Can you explain the \'fight or flight\' complex?
</item>
        <item>What makes you suspicious of someone?
</item>
        <item>What makes you suspicious of a place?
</item>
        <item>Have you tried doing anything dangerous that could risk your life?
</item>
        <item>Why are there still people who love to do dangerous sports?
</item>
        <item>Why are there people who still live in a dangerous society?
</item>
        <item>Do you think your neighborhood is dangerous?
</item>
        <item>Have you caused any danger to other people before?
</item>
        <item>What was the most dangerous thing that you have done?
</item>
        <item>Why are the rich facing a lot more danger than the poor or average people?
</item>
        <item>What time is the most dangerous time to go out?
</item>
        <item>Do you think there are dangers in your house?
</item>
        <item>What do you do when you see someone in danger?
</item>
        <item>What do you do when you see the back label of a product with a danger sign on it?
</item>
        <item>What do you do when you feel that something might happen to you?
</item>
        <item>Is there an emergency number you can call when you are in danger?
</item>
        <item>Can we stay away from danger?
</item>
        <item>Are you a person that worries about nothing or everything? Give an example of something that you worry (or don\'t worry) about.
</item>
        <item>What dangers exist when you drive? When you fly? When you take a train?
</item>
        <item>What dangers exist for babies? For children? For university students? For the elderly?
</item>
        <item>When can a government be a danger to its own people?
</item>
        <item>What kinds of people in your community have occupations related to danger?
</item>
        <item>What country do you consider the most dangerous in the world and why?
</item>
        <item>Which city in your country do you consider the most dangerous and why?
</item>
            <item>Do you think that media (TV, movies, music) can be dangerous? Why?
</item>
            <item>Have you been in a midst of danger before?
</item>
            <item>Has your put your life been put in danger before for a stranger?
</item>
            <item>Has your life been put in danger before for a stranger?
</item>
            <item>Describe a perfect date.
</item>
            <item>Describe the appearance of the person you would like to date?
</item>
            <item>Describe the character of the person you would like to date?
</item>
            <item>Do you "go Dutch" when dating?
</item>
            <item>Do you "go Dutch" when dating?
</item>
            <item>Do you believe in love at first sight?
</item>
            <item>Do you know what a \'blind date\' is?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever been on a blind date?
</item>
            <item>Did you ever arrange a blind date?
</item>
            <item>Do you drive or take the train when dating?
</item>
            <item>Do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend?
</item>
            <item>Do you think fairy tales influence our choice of a partner?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever had a crush on someone?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever hated loving someone?
</item>
            <item>Have your parents ever disapproved of any of your relationships?
</item>
            <item>How often would you like to go out on dates?
</item>
            <item>How old were you when you had your first boyfriend or girlfriend?
</item>
            <item>Is going out on dates important for you?
</item>
            <item>Is there a such thing as a perfect relationship for you?
</item>
            <item>If you could go out with anyone, who would it be?
</item>
            <item>If you are a man, and a woman asks you for a date, do you feel you should pay, or that the woman should pay?
</item>
            <item>What are some popular places to go on a date?
</item>
            <item>What characteristics do you look for in a girlfriend or boyfriend?
</item>
            <item>What do you like to talk about when on a date?
</item>
            <item>What do you look for in a girlfriend or a boyfriend?
</item>
            <item>What do you think most people talk about when dating?
</item>
            <item>What kind of clothes do you wear on a date?
</item>
            <item>What qualities are important to you in a boyfriend or girlfriend?
</item>
            <item>What was the most boring date you\'ve ever been on?
</item>
            <item>What was the most interesting date you\'ve ever been on?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever been on a diet?
</item>
            <item>How do you know if you are fat?
</item>
            <item>What is the best way to diet?
</item>
            <item>Do you think dieting can be dangerous?
</item>
            <item>Do you think fiber is important in your diet?
</item>
            <item>What kind of fiber is the best when you are trying to loose weight?
</item>
            <item>Do you think protein is important in a balanced diet?
</item>
            <item>What is a good source of protein?
</item>
            <item>Do you think people who are fat can be happy?
</item>
            <item>Do you think people are in general are gaining weight or loosing weight?
</item>
            <item>What kind of diet would you recommend to your friend?
</item>
            <item>What kind of diet would recommended for an older person(40\'s) and a younger person(teens)?
</item>
            <item>What is the difference between diet and a healthy diet?
</item>
            <item>Is there a difference between being thin and being healthy? Which one is better?
</item>
            <item>Do you think being slim equals beautiful?
</item>
            <item>Do you think there is more pressure now for teens to look slimmer?
</item>
            <item>In what way can diet influence our appearance and personality?
</item>
            <item>If you could volunteer to help after a natural disaster, what could you do?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever volunteered to help in a disaster?
</item>
            <item>Do you think the Internet can be helpful in a disaster?
</item>
            <item>Could the Internet be used for bad purposes in a disaster?
</item>
            <item>What can you do to prepare in advance for a disaster?
</item>
            <item>How much warning time do people normally have to prepare for typhoons, hurricanes, and earthquakes?
</item>
            <item>How much warning time do people normally have for tsunamis?
</item>
            <item>What sorts of preparations would you make if a typhoon was going to hit your area?
</item>
            <item>Why do people leave when a typhoon is coming?
</item>
            <item>What has your family done in the past to prepare for a disaster?
</item>
            <item>Do you have extra food and water in your house?
</item>
            <item>Do you have an electric generator in your house?
</item>
            <item>What are some essential things you would need in your house in order to be prepared for a disaster?
</item>
            <item>Do you know where the evacuation area is in your area?
</item>
            <item>What should you do if you receive a tornado warning?
</item>
            <item>What happens during an earthquake? How long does an earthquake usually last?
</item>
            <item>What happens during a tsunami?
</item>
            <item>What happens during a typhoon?
</item>
            <item>How can you prevent injury?
</item>
            <item>Where are some dangerous places to be in your house?
</item>
            <item>Where are some safe places to be in your house?
</item>
            <item>What could you say to someone who is frightened?
</item>
            <item>What are some problems people have right after a natural disaster?
</item>
            <item>What are some things you should do as soon as possible? For example,listen to the radio, watch television, check gas and water.
</item>
            <item>Do you usually remember your dreams? Why or why not? Describe some of them.
</item>
            <item>What was your nicest dream that you can remember?
</item>
            <item>Talk about the most recent dream you can remember that you have had in the past.
</item>
            <item>How do you interpret a dream? Do you use your intuition/imagination to understand it?
</item>
            <item>Do you usually read books on dream interpretation? What is your opinion on it?
</item>
            <item>Do you generally have pleasant dreams or nightmares?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever had nightmares? What were they like?
</item>
            <item>What\'s the worst nightmare you\'ve ever had?
</item>
            <item>What is "prophecy"?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever had or heard of a dream that foretold the future?
</item>
            <item>Did you know that Abraham Lincoln supposedly foresaw his own assassination in a dream? What do you think about it?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever dreamed about dead people? Is it a good signal? Why/Why not?
</item>
            <item>Do your dreams ever affect your moods? Explain.
</item>
            <item>Do you usually dream in black and white or in color?
</item>
            <item>What language do you dream in? Have you ever dreamt in a language that you don\'t speak?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever woken up from a dream "in a cold sweat"?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever had a dog or cat for a pet?
</item>
            <item>Which do you like best, dogs or cats?
</item>
            <item>What are some good names for dogs or cats?
</item>
            <item>Why would you keep a dog instead of a cat?
</item>
            <item>What can cats do that dogs can\'t?
</item>
            <item>Can you think of some reason why people don\'t keep dogs or cats?
</item>
            <item>What is a breed?
</item>
            <item>How many breeds of dogs can you name?
</item>
            <item>How many breeds of cats can you name?
</item>
            <item>Which dog breed do you think is the most intelligent and which the dumbest?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you lived in another country? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you didn\'t have any brothers? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you were taller? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you were thinner? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you studied in a different university? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you worked in a different company? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you went to a different school? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you were younger? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you were older? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you were the opposite sex? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you could cook better? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you were thinner? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish you were more fashionable? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you wish your brother would come to visit? Why?
</item>
            <item>Why do we celebrate Easter?
</item>
            <item>Do you celebrate Easter in your country?
</item>
            <item>How do you celebrate Easter in your country?
</item>
            <item>Do you have any special family traditions?
</item>
            <item>Did the original meaning of Easter get lost?
</item>
            <item>Do you know the meaning of Easter?
</item>
            <item>Where did you go to kindergarten?
</item>
            <item>Where did you go to elementary school?
</item>
            <item>Where did you go to junior high school?
</item>
            <item>Where did you go to high school?
</item>
            <item>What do you remember about your teachers?
</item>
            <item>Did you make friends in high school that you still keep in touch with?
</item>
            <item>What do you think of home schooling?
</item>
            <item>Do you think your country should spend more money on schools?
</item>
            <item>Do teachers sometimes teach things that are not important?
</item>
            <item>Are there things your school does not teach that you think it should?
</item>
            <item>What do you do to encourage yourself when going through hard times? Does it work?
        </item>
            <item>Who do you talk to for encouragement and inspiration?
</item>
            <item>What books offer encouragement and inspiration?
</item>
            <item>Which of your family members encourage you most? How?
</item>
            <item>How can discouragement help us to grow?
</item>
            <item>What do you do when you feel depressed?
</item>
            <item>What could someone do to encourage you when you feel depressed?
</item>
            <item>What are some saying in your country that bring encouragement?
</item>
            <item>What\'s the most encouraging book you\'ve ever read?
</item>
            <item>Which is better a word of encouragement or a letter of encouragement? Why?
</item>
            <item>Is time a weapon to fight discouragement with? Why? How?
</item>
            <item>How can you motivate others our yourself to have hope when there seems like there\'s no hope?
</item>
            <item>Should people just accept whatever comes there way?
</item>
            <item>What are some ways you feel you can make a difference in this world.
</item>
            <item>How can you make this world a better place?
</item>
            <item>How would you encourage a homeless bun who had no friends or relatives?
</item>
            <item>If you suddenly became handicapped, how would you encourage yourself and others?
</item>
            <item>What song encourages you most?
</item>
            <item>Who\'s music encourages you most?
</item>
            <item>What television show encourages you most?
</item>
            <item>What person has inspired you the most? How?
</item>
            <item>What celebrity has inspired you most? How
</item>
            <item>What\'s your favorite encouraging saying?
</item>
            <item>Do you encourage others when you see them crying? How?
</item>
            <item>What would you want someone to do for you if you were crying publicly because you were deeply hurt inside?
</item>
            <item>How can you fight discouraging thoughts about yourself?
</item>
            <item>When should you see a counselor or psychologist?
</item>
            <item>Can church, temples, mosque or other religious places help bring someone encouragement or inspiration?
</item>
            <item>What religious books do people turn to for encouragement and inspiration.
</item>
            <item>How can you make yourself believe more in yourself.
</item>
            <item>Do you listen to classical music? Why or why not?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever been to a play? If so, when was the last time?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever been to Disneyland?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever been to the theater?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever hosted a party?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever tried water skiing?
</item>
            <item>Have you ever used a slot machine?
</item>
            <item>How far in advance do you begin planning a vacation?
</item>
            <item>How often do you go to parties?
</item>
            <item>How often do you read comic books?
</item>
            <item>How often do you visit museums? When was the last time?
</item>
            <item>Is gambling legal where you live?
</item>
            <item>Should books be censored?
</item>
            <item>Do you often go drinking? Where? Who with? How often?
</item>
            <item>Should movies be rated? Explain.
</item>
            <item>What are some forms of gambling people do in your country?
</item>
            <item>What do you do in your spare time?
</item>
            <item>What do you like to do on a night out?
</item>
            <item>What is your favorite game? Why?
</item>
            <item>What is your favorite holiday? Why?
</item>
            <item>What kind of music do you like?
</item>
            <item>What kind of things do you like to read?
</item>
            <item>What singer would you most like to meet?
</item>
            <item>What was the last book you read?
</item>
            <item>When do you usually listen to the radio?
</item>
            <item>Where do you usually read?
</item>
            <item>Who are some of the famous actors and musicians in your country?
</item>
            <item>Who are some of your favorite actors and actresses?
</item>
            <item>Who do you think is the funniest comedian?
</item>
            <item>Who is the most popular entertainer in your country?
</item>
            <item>Why is making eye contact important?
</item>
            <item>Is making eye contact important in your culture?
</item>
            <item>Is making eye contact important in your culture?
</item>
            <item>What can you learn about a person by making eye contact?
</item>
            <item>Can you think of some situations where eye contact should not be made?
</item>
            <item>What is the difference between staring and making eye contact?
</item>
            <item>Why is making eye contact important in a job interview?
</item>
            <item>What is a fad?
</item>
            <item>Do you pay attention to fads?
</item>
            <item>What is faith?
</item>
            <item>Are friends more important than family? What do you think?
</item>
            <item>Are chores assigned to children in your family?
</item>
            <item>Do you get along well with your family?
</item>
            <item>What do you and your family like to do together?
</item>
            <item>What do you think of married couples who decide not to have any child?
</item>
            <item>Can you describe a typical family in your country?
</item>
            <item>What do you think of people who get married many times?
</item>
            <item>Do people in your country ever decide to remain single and not create a family?
</item>
            <item>Who should take care of old people?
</item>
            <item>Would you like to be famous? Why?
</item>
            <item>Are famous people happy?
</item>
            <item>Why do you think famous people are always going into rehab?
</item>
            <item>What is your favorite country? And why?
</item>
            <item>What is your favorite day of the week? Why?
</item>
            <item>What is your favorite drink in the summer?
</item>
            <item>What is your favorite holiday? Why?
</item>
            <item>What is your favorite kind of book?
</item>
            <item>Are you afraid of getting old? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you fear certain insects or animals? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you know anyone with a phobia?
</item>
            <item>Do you think young children should be allowed to watch horror movies?
</item>
            <item>Are you afraid of being ill? What disease are you most afraid of? Why?
</item>
            <item>Do you fear certain insects or animals? Why?
</item>
            <item>Are you annoyed when your partner, husband, or wife flirts with someone else ?
</item>
            <item>Do bad mannered people upset you?
</item>
            <item>Do you get angry when politicians make promises they can\'t keep?
</item>
            <item>Do you get angry when you watch the news on TV and see all the terrible things happening in the world?
</item>
            <item>Does it annoy you when shop assistants try to sell you things you don\'t need?
</item>
            <item>Does it annoy you when someone interrupts you when you are speaking?
</item>
            <item>Does it annoy you when someone knows everything better than you and says so?
</item>
            <item>Does it annoy you when you are waiting in a long queue and someone pushes in front of you?
</item>
            <item>Does it annoy you when your teacher speaks too quickly?
</item>
            <item>Does it drive you crazy to always see the same faces and read about the same celebrities in the gossip columns?
</item>
            <item>Does it drive you crazy when waiters ignore you?
</item>
            <item>Does it drive you crazy when you have invited people to dinner and they come late and the meal is spoiled?
</item>
            <item>Does it make you angry when motorists drive too closely behind you?
</item>
            <item>Does it make you angry when people make nasty comments about you ?
</item>
            <item>Does it make you angry when you have made an appointment to see the doctor at a certain time and he/she keeps you waiting for ages ?
</item>
            <item>Does it upset or annoy you when a beggar asks you for money?
</item>
            <item>Does it upset you when have to say "No" when someone asks you for help?
</item>
            <item>Does it upset you when you see homeless people?
</item>
            <item>Does it upset you when you see people hitting children or animals?
</item>
            <item>Does it upset you when you see pictures of famines in India, Africa or other countries?
</item>
            <item>Do you have a smoke alarm? How often do you check the batteries?
</item>
            <item>Do you have a fire escape plan? Does everybody in your family know where to go in case of fire?
</item>
            <item>Do you cook? If yes, what food do you cook the most often?
</item>
            <item>Do you cook? If yes, what food do you cook the most often?
</item>
            <item>How often do you eat fresh fruit?
</item>
            <item>In your opinion, what\'s the most delicious fruit?
</item>
            <item>Do you like vegetables? What\'s your favorite one?
</item>
            <item>Do you think that fruits and vegetables are good for your health? Why or why not?
</item>
            <item>Are you or would you like to be vegetarian?
</item>
            <item>How often do you drink fruit juice? What kind of fruit juice do you drink?
</item>
            <item>What kind of vegetables and fruits do you buy at the supermarket?
</item>
            <item>What the means the saying: "An apple a day keeps the doctor away?"
</item>
            <item>What are the most common fruits and vegetables in your country?
</item>
            <item>Can fruits and vegetables help you cure diseases?
</item>
            <item>Do you cultivate fruits or vegetables in your garden?
</item>
            <item>Do you like to use things that have a fruit smell? ( E.g: Perfumes, erasers, etc)
</item>
            <item>What\'s the most delicious fruit in your opinion?
</item>
            <item>Do you think that fruits and vegetables are good for your health? Why (not)?
</item>
            <item>Are you / would you like to be vegetarian?
</item>
            <item>How many vegetables and fruits do you buy at the supermarket?
</item>
            <item>What is the meaning of the saying: "An apple a day keeps the doctor away?"
</item>
            <item>Do you like to use things that have fruit smell? ( E.g: Perfumes, erasers, etc)
</item>
            <item>How will the development of robots that think change your future?
</item>
            <item>Would you like to have a robot in your house?
</item>
            <item>Do you play the lottery?
</item>
            <item>What kind of lottery do you play?
</item>
            <item>How many forms of gambling as you can think of?
</item>
            <item>Do you bet? How often? What\'s the biggest bet you ever placed?
</item>
            <item>Who suffers the most from a gambling problem?
</item>
            <item>What kinds of people do you think are more prone to developing a gambling problem?
</item>
            <item>What\'s the usual age limit for gambling games?
</item>
            <item>Do you have any pets?
</item>
            <item>What was the last book you read?
</item>
            <item>Do you like to cook?
</item>
            <item>What\'s your favorite food?
</item>
            <item>What kinds of gifts do you like to give?
</item>
            <item>If you don\'t like a gift, how long should you keep it?
</item>
            <item>What gift will you give your home-stay family when you leave?
</item>
            <item>What are your families goals?
</item>
            <item>What is your biggest goal in life?
</item>
            <item>How do you plan to achieve that goal?
</item>
            <item>What are your "short term" goals?
</item>
            <item>What are your "long term" goals?
</item>
            <item>Should parents help their children set goals?
</item>
            <item>What are your educational goals?
</item>
            <item>Is having a goal in life effective in becoming successful?
</item>
            <item>Is having a goal helpful in motivating a person?
</item>
            <item>Do you think people have fewer goals as they get older?
</item>
            <item>Do you have any goals that you feel are unrealistic?
</item>
            <item>How do people\'s goals change from country to country?
</item>
            <item>What are the main differences between male and female goals?
</item>
            <item>Which of your goals have you already achieved?
</item>
            <item>How would you feel if you failed to achieve any of your goals?
</item>
            <item>Do you think it\'s a good idea to write your goals down and tick them off as you achieve them?
</item>
            <item>How important are goals to you?
</item>
            <item>Can goals help to change your life? How?
</item>
            <item>What goals do you have in your life?
</item>
            <item>Is it important to set goals?
</item>
            <item>Do you have a five year plan for your life?
</item>
            <item>If you can\'t make your goal, how do you feel?
</item>
            <item>Are goals necessary to achieve success?
</item>
            <item>How are plans and goals related?
</item>
            <item>Are you ambitious enough to achieve the goals you set?
</item>
        <item>How will you feel,if you fail to achieve any of your goals?
</item>
        <item>What is something you never learned to do but wish you had?
</item>
        <item>Tell me about a goal that you achieved for yourself.
</item>
        <item>Do you believe that people must work hard to become successful? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Can you think of a successful person from your own county? What do they do? How do you think they did it?
</item>
        <item>What kind of success do you want in the future in your life?
</item>
        <item>What can you do now to be successful in the future?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that money and fame means success?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to gossip?
</item>
        <item>Do your friends often gossip about you?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think people like to listen to gossip ?
</item>
        <item>Why do people like to gossip about the rich and famous?
</item>
        <item>What are the most common themes for gossip?
</item>
        <item>What are some of the things you like to gossip about?
</item>
        <item>What are some ways which gossip can be harmful?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that a friend who gossips or starts rumors will ever gossip or start a rumor about you?
</item>
        <item>How would you try to resolve the problem, if you had got into trouble through gossiping?
</item>
        <item>Has answering these questions changed your attitude towards gossip?
</item>
        <item>If you discovered that someone had been gossiping about you, would you confront them?
</item>
        <item>If no-one at your high school had ever gossiped, how would it have been different?
</item>
        <item>If you heard some harmful gossip about someone you knew, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>Would you say that people who like gossiping do it because their lives are empty or because it is just a way of entertainment?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had problems because of gossip?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if someone gossips about you?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever told a rumor that got someone into trouble?
</item>
        <item>Has discussing gossip and changed your attitude towards gossip?
</item>
        <item>If no one at your high school had ever gossiped, how would your school be different?
</item>
        <item>Do you have any bad habits?
</item>
        <item>Do you cut people off in the middle of their stories and conversations?
</item>
        <item>What unusual habits do you observe in your family members? Do they bother you?
</item>
        <item>Which bad habit do you think would be the most difficult to get rid of? Why?
</item>
        <item>Which good habit do you think would be the most difficult to develop? Why?
</item>
        <item>Which habit is the most important for parents to set as an example of for their children?
</item>
        <item>Do you cut people off in the middle of there stories and conversations?
</item>
        <item>What is happiness for you?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is the color for happiness?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that happiness lies within you? Or does it depend upon other people and external things?
</item>
        <item>Can money buy happiness?
</item>
        <item>Is happiness a state of mind?
</item>
        <item>What are the three most important things for you to be happy?
</item>
        <item>Is happiness relative, that is, does it have a different meaning for each person?
</item>
        <item>Are single people happy?
</item>
        <item>Would you be happier with a soul mate or single?
</item>
        <item>Does having an animal/pet make you happy?
</item>
        <item>What is the effect that animals/pets have on people to make them feel happy?
</item>
        <item>What makes you happy?
</item>
        <item>When was the happiest time of your childhood?
</item>
        <item>Can you be happy if you are rich?
</item>
        <item>Can you be happy is you are poor?
</item>
        <item>How can you become happy again when you are sad?
</item>
        <item>Is happiness a goal?
</item>
        <item>How often do you feel really happy?
</item>
        <item>Are you very happy most of the time?
</item>
        <item>What makes you unhappy?
</item>
        <item>What\'s the most miserable you\'ve been?
</item>
        <item>How happy are you compared with your friends?
</item>
        <item>Do you wake up happy every morning?
</item>
        <item>Do you agree that older people are less happy?
</item>
        <item>What is there to be happy about in the world today?
</item>
        <item>What affects your levels of happiness?
</item>
        <item>Does your happiness change during different times of the day, week, month or year?
        </item>
        <item>What is or was the happiest time of your life?
</item>
        <item>Do you need money to be happy?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of the idea of a government Happiness Minister who is responsible for the happiness of the population?
</item>
        <item>Do you think some nations are happier than others?
</item>
        <item>What is missing in your life that would make you very happy?
</item>
        <item>Why are teenagers some of the happiest people in the world?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever appreciated a sunset?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been a guest at a surprise party?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been in a fist fight?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been on TV?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever broken a bone?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever broken up with someone?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever called your boyfriend or girlfriend by the wrong name?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever called your girlfriend/boyfriend "Honey?"
</item>
        <item>Have you ever cheated on an exam?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever cried in public and embarrassed yourself?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever dated someone from another race, culture or religion?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever done something silly that you wish you had not done?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever driven a sports car?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever eaten in a restaurant and realized you have no money with you?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever finished eating in a restaurant, and you realized you forgot your wallet?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever eaten something that you thought you wouldn\'t like, but found out that you actually liked it?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever fallen asleep and forgotten where you were?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever fallen asleep while taking a bath?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever given a false excuse to get out of something you didn\'t want to do? If so, tell us about it.
</item>
        <item>Have you ever given a ring (or other jewelry) to your girlfriend/boyfriend?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever gone mountain climbing?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever dreamt of a ghost being in your bedroom and then waking up and finding yourself looking around for the ghost?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever gone to greet a friend or family member then noticed it was someone else?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever gotten sunburnt at the tanning saloon and gone back the next day?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever played a joke on one of your teachers?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever thought of something funny and started laughing out loud in the presence of others?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been in the shower when there was an earthquake?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever ripped off your pants while dancing?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever kissed somebody by mistake?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever laughed until tears came from your eyes?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever fallen asleep while talking on the phone?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever sprained your ankle/wrist? How did it happen?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever written an article for a newspaper?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen a car accident?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever called your school\'s principal?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever received more than 10 cards on Valentines day?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been on the radio or television?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever ridden on an ostrich? A camel? A cow?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever shaken hands with a monkey?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever received a love letter?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen a tornado?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had an electricity blackout while taking a shower?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever picked you\'re nose in public?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been on the radio? T.V?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever ridden on an ostrich?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever tried any extreme sports?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever shot a gun at a tree or a target?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever played an instrument in public?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever sung in public?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever talked "baby-talk" to your pet?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever given special nicknames to your pet that were completely different than their first given name?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever kept a special blanket or bed for your pet to sleep on?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever let your pet sleep in or on your bed with you?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been mugged?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever played in a movie?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever made somebody cry?
</item>
        <item>Can you describe each room of your house?
</item>
        <item>What does the outside of your house look like?
</item>
        <item>Where do you park your car at your house
</item>
        <item>Do you like the place where you are living? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>What is your favorite room in your house? Why?
</item>
        <item>How are homes different in your home country and in this country?
</item>
        <item>How have you changed your home since you\'ve started living there?
</item>
        <item>How much is your rent? (Some people may not consider this to be a polite question.)
</item>
        <item>If you could change anything about your present home, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>Is your home in a convenient location?
</item>
        <item>What changes would you like to make to your home?
</item>
        <item>What do you like about your home? What don\'t you like?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is the worst color for a living room?
</item>
        <item>What things in your home couldn\'t you live without?
</item>
        <item>What things in your house could you easily live without?
</item>
        <item>Who lives with you? / Who do you live with?
</item>
        <item>What strange materials do you know of that have been used to make houses?
</item>
        <item>Could you build a house for yourself? How would you do it? (you cannot have a builder help you)
</item>
        <item>How can houses be made more environmentally friendly?
</item>
        <item>Give some reasons why people become homeless.
</item>
        <item>What problems do home owners have? What can they do about them?
</item>
        <item>Is it better to rent or buy? Give reasons for your answer.
</item>
        <item>What is humorous to you?
</item>
        <item>What is your favorite comedy?
</item>
        <item>Who is your favorite comedian?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about a time when you were very funny?
</item>
        <item>What kind of humor do you like? Do you like many kinds?
</item>
        <item>Why do people say laughter is the best medicine?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about a time when you laughed at yourself?
</item>
        <item>What type of humor do you like?
</item>
        <item>Why do people immigrate to other countries?
</item>
        <item>What is the reason you moved out of your country to move here?
</item>
        <item>Is immigration from one country to another a problem? In what ways do you see it as a problem?
</item>
        <item>Do you know any immigrants?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that immigrants are treated well in most countries?
</item>
        <item>Do you think there is a relation between immigration and crime?
</item>
        <item>Should any government limit the number of immigrants entering the country? What would be a good number?
</item>
        <item>Is local culture threatened by immigration?
</item>
        <item>How far should immigrants retain their culture?
</item>
        <item>Should immigrants have the same rights as native citizens?
</item>
        <item>Is there a difference between political and economic immigration?
</item>
        <item>What should be done with the illegal immigrants entering a country?
</item>
        <item>Should the country of origin of illegal immigrants be held responsible?
</item>
        <item>Do immigrants have a good or bad reputation in your part of the country?
</item>
        <item>Should students be allowed to wear clothes with cultural or religious symbolism at school?
</item>
        <item>Do you think immigrants are treated with more suspicion now than they were a year ago?
</item>
        <item>Do you know anyone that is married to an immigrant?
</item>
        <item>Do you know any people who have emigrated from your country?
</item>
        <item>What would be some of the issues that would concern you about emigrating?
</item>
        <item>Do immigrants in your community isolate themselves into a certain area?
</item>
        <item>How would you help an immigrant learn the local language?
</item>
        <item>How does an immigrant become a citizen in your country?
</item>
        <item>Do you often use the Internet?
</item>
        <item>When did you first use the Internet?
</item>
        <item>About how many hours a day do you use the Internet?
</item>
        <item>About how many hours a week do you use the Internet?
</item>
        <item>Who uses the Internet the most in your family?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever bought something using the Internet?
</item>
        <item>How often do you use the internet?
</item>
        <item>Do you think our lives have been improved by the Internet?
</item>
        <item>Do you have any ideas or ambitions to start an Internet company?
</item>
        <item>Do men and women use the internet for different purposes?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me something about yourself?
</item>
        <item>Why do you want to work for us?
</item>
        <item>What is a leader?
</item>
        <item>Who are the first leaders who come to your mind?
</item>
        <item>What makes people great leaders?
</item>
        <item>What are the qualities or characteristics that every leader should have?
</item>
        <item>Are some people natural leaders and other people natural followers? Why?
</item>
        <item>What are some of the biggest challenges of leading a country like China?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be a leader in China? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Why do some people think it\'s a bad thing to always follow other people?
</item>
        <item>What characteristics does a bad leader have?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever studied a martial art?
</item>
        <item>Can you name any Japanese/Chinese/Korean martial arts?
</item>
        <item>Which martial art is best in your opinion? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you like fighting?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever been in a fight? Did you win?
</item>
        <item>Do you think its useful to study martial arts?
</item>
        <item>Who is your favorite kung fu movie actor/actress?
</item>
        <item>Do you like Hong Kong kung fu movies?
</item>
        <item>What is your favorite kung fu movie?
</item>
        <item>Do you know anything about martial arts history? What?
</item>
        <item>Do you think its important to preserve tradition in martial arts?
</item>
        <item>How many different kinds of kung fu have you heard of?
</item>
        <item>Do you know how to use any traditional weapons?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is life all about?
</item>
        <item>What do you feel most people\'s lives are driven by?
</item>
        <item>What image or metaphor has best described your life? A race, a circus or something else?
</item>
        <item>What if life on earth is really preparation for eternity, how would people act differently?
</item>
        <item>What is your opinion on why a lot of people have trouble believing in God?
</item>
        <item>Which is easier for people, public or private worship?
</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy meeting new people?
</item>
        <item>What are some good things to ask someone you just met?
</item>
        <item>What are some things you shouldn\'t ask people you just met?
</item>
        <item>Is it OK to ask a person\'s age in your country?
</item>
        <item>Are you nervous when you are introduced to someone new?
</item>
        <item>What are some ways to overcome being nervous about meeting new people?
</item>
        <item>About how many new people do you meet a week?
</item>
        <item>Where are some good places to meet people?
</item>
        <item>How important are first impressions to you?
</item>
        <item>What do you do if you forget the name of someone you\'ve just been introduced to?
</item>
        <item>What kind of people do you like to meet?
</item>
        <item>Who was the last new person you met and where did you meet them?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever experienced being completely wrong in your first impression?
</item>
        <item>Do you usually shake hands with when you meet a new person?
</item>
        <item>If you want to get to know people at a party would you go first to people of your own age or people of your own sex?
</item>
        <item>What is the favorite topic for new acquaintances in your country?
</item>
        <item>If you are looking for a shallow relationship, where do you usually go to meet people?
</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy meeting new people?
</item>
        <item>Do you feel you are outgoing or shy around people? How do you usually act?
</item>
        <item>What are some good things to ask someone you have just met?
</item>
        <item>What are some things you shouldn\'t ask people you just met?
</item>
        <item>Is it OK to ask a person for their age in your country? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>About how many new people do you meet a week?
</item>
        <item>Where are some good places to meet people?
</item>
        <item>How important are first impressions to you?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever experienced being completely wrong in your first impression?
</item>
        <item>What do you do if you forget the name of someone you\'ve just been introduced to?
</item>
        <item>What kind of people do you like to meet?
</item>
        <item>Who was the last new person you met and where did you meet them? Have you seen them again?
</item>
        <item>What do people do when they meet a new person in your culture?
</item>
        <item>Is it OK to touch another person when you first meet them in your culture?
</item>
        <item>Do you ever shake hands with when you meet a new person in your culture?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to shake hands when you meet new people?
</item>
        <item>What is a favorite topic for new acquaintances of your age in your country?
</item>
        <item>If you are looking for a shallow relationship, where can you go to meet people?
</item>
        <item>If you are looking for a good friend, where can you go to meet people?
</item>
        <item>In your country, how do you know if you can trust a person that you meet?
</item>
        <item>How do you know if you can trust a person that you have met?
</item>
        <item>What is one thing that many people don\'t know about you?
</item>
        <item>How far apart do people stand from each other when they talk in your culture?
</item>
        <item>Is it impolite to say "No" in your culture if you don\'t know someone very well?
</item>
        <item>Do people in your culture use a lot of body language when they communicate, or do they keep their bodies relatively still?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever done meditation? What was your experience?

</item>
        <item>In what ways are mind and body connected?
</item>
        <item>Are you good at saving money?
</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy shopping?
</item>
        <item>How do you usually spend your money? What do you usually buy?
</item>
        <item>Do you ever give money to beggars on the street? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Do you ever give money to charity? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever borrowed money from someone? Who? What did you need the money for?
</item>
        <item>Have your parents ever given you a credit card to pay for something? What did you buy?
</item>
        <item>What bank do you use? Do you like the service you receive?
</item>
        <item>Do you ever gamble? Did you win anything?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever had any money stolen from you? What happened?
</item>
        <item>Can a person be rich without having a lot of money or possessions? How?
</item>
        <item>How important is money to you? If you had little money, could you be happy?
</item>
        <item>How much do you spend each month on food? Where do you usually buy food?
</item>
        <item>Have you ever tried to lose weight?
</item>
        <item>Do you feel motivated when learning something new?
</item>
        <item>Do you find that motivated people are more successful than unmotivated people?
</item>
        <item>Tell three things that make you to be motivated.
</item>
        <item>Does motivation affect learning?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think the center of the movie industry in the United States began in Hollywood, southern California, next to Los Angeles?
</item>
        <item>Do you like Hollywood movies? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>What kind of information about the United States have you learned by watching Hollywood movies?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that movies from different countries can teach us about other cultures?
</item>
        <item>What kinds of movies are popular in your country?
</item>
        <item>What do the popular movies in your country show about your culture?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it is right for Hollywood movies to be the movies that are seen most around the world?
</item>
        <item>Why do you think that Harry Potter books and movies have been so popular all around the world?
</item>
        <item>Is the movie industry in your country strong? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Does the film industry in your country make good movies? Give some examples.
</item>
        <item>Do you think that the movies from your country can be popular in other parts of the world if they have subtitles or are dubbed in different languages? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>What is your all-time favorite movie?
</item>
        <item>What is your favorite movie?
</item>
        <item>Do you like to watch horror movies?
</item>
        <item>Do you prefer fiction or nonfiction books? How about movies?
</item>
        <item>Do you think movies have been developing technology or technology has been developing movies?
</item>
        <item>What kind of movie do you like?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be an actor/actress? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Which horror movie is the scariest? Why?
</item>
        <item>Which movie has the best story ? Tell me about it.
</item>
        <item>Have you ever fallen asleep in the middle of a film? Why?
</item>
        <item>Which movie has the best story? Tell me about it.
</item>
        <item>What kind of music do you like?
</item>
        <item>Are you a good singer?
</item>
        <item>Can you concentrate on other things when you are listening to music?
</item>
        <item>Do you prefer listening to songs in your own language or in another language? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that people form different cultures react to music in different ways?
</item>
        <item>What kind or style of music would it be weird for your parents to listen to? Why?
</item>
        <item>If you could be any musician in the world, who would you be and why?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me some things about your neighborhood?
</item>
        <item>What are the advantages and disadvantages of your neighborhood?
</item>
        <item>What would you change about your neighborhood?
</item>
        <item>What types of facilities are available near to you?
</item>
        <item>How far are you from the city center?
</item>
        <item>Do you like living in your neighborhood or do you not have much choice?
</item>
        <item>What do you like about your community?
</item>
        <item>How many of your neighbors do you know?

</item>
        <item>Are there old people living in your community? Tell me about them.
</item>
        <item>Are there little children in your community? Tell me about them.
</item>
        <item>What do the people in your community do for recreation?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is the most important thing about community?
</item>
        <item>Does your community have special days to get together?
</item>
        <item>Does your community have meetings?
</item>
        <item>Is there a neighborhood watch program in your community?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to raise your children in a community like yours? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>Is your community afraid of strangers?
</item>
        <item>Does your community welcome strangers?
</item>
        <item>What is the role of newspapers in society?
</item>
        <item>Why do we buy newspapers?
</item>
        <item>Will newspapers disappear in the future?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that the news is necessary? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>What would the world be like without news?
</item>
        <item>Do you think the news tells us just information without giving its opinion?
</item>
        <item>Should the news give an opinion?
</item>
        <item>Do you think the news influences people too much?
</item>
        <item>What do you think is the most important thing the news should report?
</item>
        <item>What was the most memorable news you ever watched?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider being a journalist? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>If someone asked you to be a journalist, what kind of stories would you write about?
</item>
        <item>Would you prefer being a newscaster or a journalist?
</item>
        <item>When you watch the news, are you interested in the story or the newscaster who presents it?
</item>
        <item>Do you think journalists tell the truth when they write?
</item>
        <item>Do you think journalists add more information to make the story interesting?
</item>
        <item>Do you believe journalists exaggerate what they write about?
</item>
        <item>Do you believe that journalists write stories so they can be important and noticed on television/magazines/newspapers etc?
</item>
        <item>Do you trust the information you get from the news?
</item>
        <item>Are any of the things similar to New Year\'s celebrations in your country?
</item>
        <item>What traditional ways of welcoming the New Year do you have in your family or in your region?
</item>
        <item>How old are your New Year traditions? Did your grandparents celebrate in the same way?
</item>
        <item>Are children allowed to stay up late on New Year\'s Eve in your country?
</item>
        <item>Are there any special meals or activities for New Year\'s day?
</item>
        <item>What is the difference between our daydreams and our dreams at night?
</item>
        <item>If you had to change one Olympic sport, which sport would you take away and which sport would you add?
</item>
        <item>What is the most difficult Olympic sport?
</item>
        <item>If we held the Olympics tomorrow in this class, in which sport would you win the gold?
</item>
        <item>What are some characteristics of your personality?
</item>
        <item>What are some things that make you angry?
</item>
        <item>What makes you happy?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be different?
</item>
        <item>Are you a determined person? Are you a stubborn person?
</item>
        <item>Do you consider yourself selfish ? Why?
</item>
        <item>Is your personality suited to your job?
</item>
        <item>In what way has your personality changed? Why has it changed??
</item>
        <item>Do you think you can change a major characteristic of your personality if you try?
</item>
        <item>Do you think you have an unusual personality? Why?
</item>
        <item>If you could change any aspect of your personality, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>What sort of things would you do to amuse yourself during a car journey?
</item>
        <item>What personality traits do you consider important in a good friend / a boss / a partner?
</item>
        <item>Do you consider yourself to be even-tempered?
</item>
        <item>What is one thing that many people don\'t know about you?
</item>
        <item>What do the colors in your home country\'s flag represent?
</item>
        <item>Do you think birth order makes a difference in your personality?
</item>
        <item>Would you like to be a police officer?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that it is a very dangerous job?
</item>
        <item>Have the police ever helped you? How?
</item>
        <item>Did you vote in the last election?
</item>
        <item>How old were you when you first voted?
</item>
        <item>What is the minimum voting age in your country?
</item>
        <item>What type of political system does your country have?
</item>
        <item>What different types of governments are there?
</item>
        <item>What is poverty?
</item>
        <item>What kind of problems do poor people have?
</item>
        <item>Why are people hungry?
</item>
        <item>Do you feel sorry for people who live on the street?
</item>
        <item>Are people who live on the street necessarily lazy?
</item>
        <item>Do you believe that the rich are growing richer, and the poor are growing poorer?
</item>
        <item>Shouldn\'t all people work for a living?
</item>
        <item>Would you pay more taxes, if this would eliminate poverty by creating jobs for everyone?
</item>
        <item>Will there always be poverty in the world?
</item>
        <item>Should countries send troops to foreign countries to fight terrorism, or should governments fight poverty around the world instead?
</item>
        <item>Are there more important issues than poverty? If so, name them in order of importance.
</item>
        <item>Why does every country in the world have poor people?
</item>
        <item>What do you think about people receiving welfare?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of countries that do not have a welfare system?
</item>
        <item>What do you think about people who work for cash and receive welfare as well?
</item>
        <item>What do you think of governments who put the homeless in jails or even torture or kill them?
</item>
        <item>Do you think the government has the right to read your email?
</item>
        <item>What do you think about being fingerprinted when you enter a country?
</item>
        <item>What is race?
</item>
        <item>What races do we have in the world?
</item>
        <item>What is ethnicity?
</item>
        <item>Is religion important to you?
</item>
        <item>Why do people renovate their house?
</item>
        <item>At this stage of your life, are you beginning to make plans for your retirement years? Why?
</item>
        <item>What is the difference between science and technology?
</item>
        <item>In your opinion,what is the greatest technological invention? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you think people should be allowed to clone people or organs of people? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you think using cell phones too much is bad for our physical or mental health? Why?
</item>
        <item>Do you think money should be spent to explore space or is it better spent helping people on earth? Why?
</item>
        <item>When you meet someone new, are there some things that you want to keep secret or private? Why? What?
</item>
        <item>What are some things that you need to consider when starting your own business?
        </item>
        <item>Is it better to be single or married? Why?
</item>
        <item>Can people smoke anywhere in your country?
</item>
        <item>Do you think it\'s acceptable for parents to use corporal punishment as a means of discipline? Why/why not?
</item>
        <item>Do you think that minorities should be given job priority because of their race? Why/why not?
</item>
        <item>What sport do you think is the most dangerous?
</item>
        <item>What sport do you think is the most expensive?
</item>
        <item>What is stress?
</item>
        <item>What causes stress?
</item>
        <item>How do you recognize stress in your life?
</item>
        <item>Do you think stress is ever good, useful, or necessary?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four TV shows you love to watch?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four places you would like to go on vacation?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four places you have been on vacation?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four of your favorite websites?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four of your favorite ESL websites.?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four websites you visit daily?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four ski areas you would like to ski at?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four pets you have had?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four meals you prepare for your family?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four things you do not like to talk about?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four of your favorite store to buy clothes in?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four ways to find a boyfriend or girlfriend?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about four restaurants near your house where you eat?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three names you go by?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things you like about yourself?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things you dislike about yourself?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three parts of your heritage?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things that scare you?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things you need to do everyday?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things you are wearing now?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three of your favorite band that you listen to now?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three of your favorite songs?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things you want to do in the next twelve months?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things you want in a relationship?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things you can\'t do?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three of your hobbies?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things you want to do right now?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three things you want to do before the end of the year?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three cities you would like to visit?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three of your favorite things to eat?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk three people who have influenced your life?
</item>
        <item>Can you talk about three of your most prized possessions?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something you love?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something you hate?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something you really care about?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about someone you dislike?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about a dream you\'ve had?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about a goal you have?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about yourself?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about your childhood?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about your family?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about your parents?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about your pet?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something you believe in?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about a place you\'ve visited?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about an accident you\'ve seen?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about a time when you were happy?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about a time when you were sad?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about a time when you were excited?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about a time when you were frightened?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about your favorite pastime?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about chocolate?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about rainy days?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something beautiful?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something ugly?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something delicious?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something pleasant?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something boring?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something with four legs?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something with a tail?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about something spicy?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell about your education?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your work?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a teacher you had?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a boss you had?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about the hardest thing you ever had to do?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a time you lied?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about something you regret?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a mistake you made?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about someone in your family?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your favorite book?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about someone you envy?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about something you\'ve achieved?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about the worst punishment you had when you were a child?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your first kiss (if it is possible)?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about someone you admire?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about the last book you\'ve read / movie you\'ve watched?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a country or place you would like to visit and why?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your favorite music / song / band?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about something you would happily do again?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your worst vacation?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a problem you have now?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about gambling?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a collection you have?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your first boyfriend/girlfriend?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your first kiss?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a prize you won?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your favorite restaurant?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your favorite movie?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your dreams?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your dream car?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your country?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your fears?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your hopes?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about love?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about the most important lesson you\'ve learnt in life so far?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your home town?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your computer system?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about something you would never do, if you have chance to come back life again?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a time in your life when you were very, very busy?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about what your God is like?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your past relationships?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about something that scares you?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about one of your grandparents?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about the hardest decision you have ever made?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a recent embarrassing moment you\'ve had lately?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a time you felt really proud?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about a famous historical person (living or dead) who if you had the opportunity, you\'d like to interview?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your hometown?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your job / school?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your friends?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about your family?
</item>
        <item>Can you tell me about what you enjoy doing most in your free time?
</item>
        <item>If you had only 24 hours to live, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If a classmate asked you for the answer to a question during an exam while the teacher was not looking, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If someone\'s underwear was showing, would you tell them?
</item>
        <item>If the whole world were listening, what would you say?
</item>
        <item>If one song were to describe your life, what song would it be?
</item>
        <item>If you bumped your car into another car, but nobody saw you do it, would you leave your name and address?
</item>
        <item>If you could ask God any one question, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>If you could be an animal, what animal would you be?
</item>
        <item>If you could be a bird, what bird would you choose to be?
</item>
        <item>If you could be a plant, what plant would you choose to be?
</item>
        <item>If you could be a super hero, which super hero would you be?
</item>
        <item>If you could be another man or woman for a day, who would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you could be another person for a day, who would you be?
</item>
        <item>If you could be invisible for a day what would you do and why?
</item>
        <item>If you could change one thing about your spouse or significant other, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>If you could change one thing about yourself, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>If you could change one thing in the world, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>If you could choose how you were going to die, what would you choose your death to be?
</item>
        <item>If you could choose to live on a different planet, which one would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you could commit any crime and get away with it, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you could date a celebrity, who would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you could have only one food for the rest of your life (assuming that this strange situation would not affect your health), which food would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you could hear what someone is thinking for a day, who would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you could live anywhere, where would you live?
</item>
        <item>If you could meet any famous person, dead or alive, who would it be and why?
</item>
        <item>If you could spend a day with any celebrity, who would it be and what questions would you ask that person?
</item>
        <item>If you could take a vacation anywhere in the world for any length of time, where would you go?
</item>
        <item>if you could go anywhere in the world for a holiday, where would you go?
</item>
        <item>If you could travel back in time, where would you go?
</item>
        <item>If you didn\'t have enough money to get the bus home what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you discovered a new island, what would you name it and why?
</item>
        <item>If you got arrested for murder, whom would you call with your telephone call from prison? And why?
</item>
        <item>If you had an accident and you had to be at home to recover for a long time, what would you do to relieve the boredom?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you were at home at night alone and you heard a noise in your flat/house that seemed to be footsteps?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you found the wallet of your next door neighbor who you hated?
</item>
        <item>If you could have any car you wanted, which car would you choose? Would it be practical or flashy?
</item>
        <item>If your car broke down on the motorway, what would you do? Would you try to fix it yourself?
</item>
        <item>If you could solve the problem of hunger in the third world or repair the ozone, which would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you could stop a bad habit that you have, what would you stop?
</item>
        <item>If you could go back to any moment in history, where would you go?
</item>
        <item>If you could be famous (a household name), what would you like to be famous for?
</item>
        <item>If you were on holiday and you lost your passport, would you know what to do?
</item>
        <item>If you were offered a job in another part of the country, would you be willing to take the job, assuming that the pay is very good?
</item>
        <item>If your partner were offered a job in another part of the country, which was well paid, would you be willing to change places?
</item>
        <item>If you were in the bank and somebody started to hold up the bank, what would you do? How would you react?
</item>
        <item>If you had one wish, what would you wish for?
</item>
        <item>If you could only listen to one song for the rest of your life, which song would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If only one book existed, which book would you like it to be?
</item>
        <item>If you could do any job, what would you like to do?
</item>
        <item>If you could move anywhere, where would you like to live?
</item>
        <item>If you found a suitcase full of $1,000,000, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you found a wallet with 1,000 in it, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you had the opportunity to be different, what would you change?
</item>
        <item>If you had time machine, where would you go and why?
</item>
        <item>If you had to choose between love and no money or money and no love for the rest of your life, which would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you had to choose, would you give up your sight or your hearing?
</item>
        <item>If you saw a robbery, would you report it?
</item>
        <item>If you saw your zipper was down and people had noticed, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you were candy, what candy would you be?
</item>
        <item>If you were a monster, what monster would you be?
</item>
        <item>If you were a toy, what toy would you be?
</item>
        <item>If you were abducted by aliens, would you tell anybody? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>If you were American/Chinese/Mexican, how would your life be different?
</item>
        <item>If you were asked to choose which time period you would like to live in, which century would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you were asked to speak to a graduating class, what would you say?
</item>
        <item>If you were given a chance to go to the moon, would you go? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>If you were given a choice between being given great wisdom or great wealth, which would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you were given an opportunity to be born again, in which country would you like to be born?
</item>
        <item>If you were given an opportunity to be born again, what kind of person would you choose to be?
</item>
        <item>If you were given one million dollars, what would you buy?
</item>
        <item>If you were given the opportunity to be born again, how would you change how you lived?
</item>
        <item>If you were given the opportunity to mold your partner the way you wanted, how would you mold your partner?
</item>
        <item>If you were given three wishes, what would you wish for?
</item>
        <item>If you were God, how would you transmit or let people know your message?
</item>
        <item>If you were going to a deserted island and could only take three things with you, what would you take? Why?
</item>
        <item>If you were marooned on a desert island with one other person how would you survive?
</item>
        <item>If you were invited to have tea with the Queen of England, what would say?
</item>
        <item>If you were the leader of your country, what would you change?
</item>
        <item>If you were the President of the United States, what problem or concern would you work on first?
</item>
        <item>If you were told that you were going to die tomorrow, what would you do today?
</item>
        <item>If you were walking through the forest and you suddenly saw a tiger, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you woke up suddenly because your house was on fire, which three things would you save as you ran outside?
</item>
        <item>If you worked for a store and you saw another employee steal something, would you tell the manager?
</item>
        <item>If your friend could not have a child, would you carry her child for her?
</item>
        <item>If you saw someone in public with toilet paper stuck to their shoe, would you tell them?
</item>
        <item>If you could change one thing that you did that was bad, perhaps a crime or some wrong you did to another person, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>If you were told you had a terminal illness and had six months to live. What three things would be most important for you to do?
</item>
        <item>If your doctor has just told you that you have a month to live, what would you do in that stretch of time?
</item>
        <item>What if you have to sacrifice yourself for the sake of saving your mother? What would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you could live perfectly well without sleeping, if you had no need to sleep at all, how would you spend all your nights?
</item>
        <item>If you could be married with a foreign (man/woman), how do you think your life would change?
</item>
        <item>If you had a chance to choose a poor (man/woman) as a (husband/wife) from your culture or a rich (man/woman) from another culture, which would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you got into traffic accident, what would you do first?
</item>
        <item>If you could be God, what would you do for humanity?
</item>
        <item>If you could receive praise from a person, what person would it be?
</item>
        <item>If you were a color, what color would you be and why?
</item>
        <item>If you were a fruit, what fruit would you be and why?
</item>
        <item>If you had a time machine and you could be transported to any time, the past or the future. What time would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you could have dinner with anyone (dead or alive), who would you choose, and why?
</item>
        <item>If you could live forever on earth as it is now, would you? Why or why not?
</item>
        <item>If you were the Queen or King of Britain for a day, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you were the President of the USA for a day, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you had to spend 100 days on a desert island, what five things would you take with you and why?
</item>
        <item>If you were down on your luck, would you seek the advice of a palm reader,
</item>
        <item>If the U.S. attacked North Korea, what would happen?
</item>
        <item>If you lost your bathing suit while you were swimming, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you woke up one morning to find you had switched bodies with someone you know. what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you could have any one supernatural power (flying, being invisible), which would you choose and why?
</item>
        <item>If you could say a sentence which the whole world could hear, what would you say?
</item>
        <item>If you were a loin would you like to eat a man?
</item>
        <item>If you could choose to live anywhere in the world where would you prefer to live?
</item>
        <item>If your spouse cheated on you, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you were given a choice to live as long as you want, how long would you like to live?
</item>
        <item>If we could live for 300 years, what would the life be like?
</item>
        <item>If you could change sexes for a day, would you? What would you do if you did swap?
</item>
        <item>If you were a famous film star, what crazy things would you ask for in your dressing room?
</item>
        <item>If you could stop time, what would you do and why?
</item>
        <item>If you had to kill a highly religious figure to save your terminal son. Would you do it?
</item>
        <item>If you could relive any moment in your life which moment would it be and why?
</item>
        <item>If you were given choice to live as long as you like, how long would you like to live?
</item>
        <item>If you could change one thing about your life what would it be and why?
</item>
        <item>What if you could relive any moment in your life which moment would it be and why?
</item>
        <item>If you could be a character from a movie, who would you be and why ?
</item>
        <item>If you could only see three people for the rest of your life who would it be?
</item>
        <item>If you were an English teacher, what would you do to improve your students\' English?
</item>
        <item>If you could be famous throughout history for one thing, what would it be?
</item>
        <item>If you had to lose an arm or a leg, which would you choose. Why?
</item>
        <item>If you could be famous, but poor forever would you do it?
</item>
        <item>If you could have the chance to re-choose your spouse, what kind would you choose?
</item>
        <item>If you were a hotdog and you were starving, would you eat yourself?
</item>
        <item>If electricity weren\'t invented yet, how would your life be different?
</item>
        <item>If you were to be killed, what part of your body would you donate and why?
</item>
        <item>If you went to the toilet and then discovered that there was no paper, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you woke up in bed and saw a huge spider walking over you, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>If you could have a party and invite anyone (dead or alive), which people would you invite?
</item>
        <item>If you could eat only one food for the rest of your what food would you choose and why?
</item>
        <item>What if your cell phone fell in the toilet, what would you do?
</item>
        <item>What would you like to do in the future?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you were rich?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you were poor?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you were the principal of your school?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you won a lottery?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you were told you had one month to live?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you lost your passport?
</item>
        <item>What would you do if you were kidnapped?
</item>
        <item>What would you choose to have written on your gravestone when you die?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever donate blood?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider being a farmer?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider getting plastic surgery?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever donate a kidney or another vital organ?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever donate an organ in order to save other person\'s life?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever give money to a charity?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever marry someone your parents didn\'t approve of?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever drive a car if you had forgotten your license at home?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever drive at night with only one headlight?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever drive your car with a flat tire?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever walk home alone at night?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever lie to your parents?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider going bungee jumping?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider going skydiving?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever eat rice with sugar?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever feed the animals at the zoo?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever get hair implants?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever give money to a panhandler? (a beggar)
</item>
        <item>Would you ever go skinny dipping? (swim naked)
</item>
        <item>Would you ever lie to help a friend?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever paint your living room black?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever pick up a hitchhiker?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever slap someone for something they said?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever smoke in a no smoking area?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever spank your child?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever steal from your family or friends?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever "take a bullet" for someone else?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever walk downtown without any shoes on your feet?
</item>
        <item>Would you eat a live cricket for $500? If not, how much money would it take?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider killing yourself?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever eat human flesh?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever resort to cannibalism if it were the only option left to stay alive?
</item>
        <item>Would you divorce your husband/wife if your favorite celebrity wanted to marry you?
</item>
        <item>Would you name your children after favorite characters in movies or books?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever pull over and help someone on the side of the road?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever say yes to someone even if you meant no?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider plastic surgery if a friend suggested it to you?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider writing your own book?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever try staying in the jungle for a month?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider surrogacy?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider being a surrogate mother yourself?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider egg or sperm donation?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever drink your own urine?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever cheat on your husband/wife?
</item>
        <item>Would you ever consider being a criminal?
</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>